Ramana	B-PERSON_NAME
Balasubramanian	I-PERSON_NAME
Wingify	B-COMPANY
,	O
Navi	B-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Ulwe	I-LOCATION
LG	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
BI	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
B.P.Ed.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Threat	B-FIELD
Intelligence	I-FIELD
,	O
Rajalakshmi	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.3%	B-GRADE
Sonali	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Ansys	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Shimla	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Phoenix	B-CLIENT
Contact	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
DevOps	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
t	O
November	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Blockchain)	I-DEGREE
–	O
EdTech	B-FIELD
h,	O
NIPER	B-INSTITUTION
Ahmedabad	I-INSTITUTION
d,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
3,	O
8.6/10	B-GRADE
0	O
Safdar	B-PERSON_NAME
Dey	I-PERSON_NAME
Conduent	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Nalgonda	B-LOCATION
Peter	B-CLIENT
England	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Library	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Water	B-FIELD
Quality	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
56.4%	B-GRADE
Sarojini	B-PERSON_NAME
Shah	I-PERSON_NAME
Zealous	B-COMPANY
System	I-COMPANY
,	O
Vidisha	B-LOCATION
Delphi	B-CLIENT
Technologies	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Robotics	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Distance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Quantization	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
North	B-INSTITUTION
Eastern	I-INSTITUTION
Hill	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
58.3%	B-GRADE
Lisha	B-PERSON_NAME
Malik	I-PERSON_NAME
Ultrahuman	B-COMPANY
,	O
Dantewada	B-LOCATION
GE	B-CLIENT
Grid	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
PLC	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
B.Pharm	B-DEGREE
(Hons)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Health	B-FIELD
Informatics	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Oxford	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.8/10	B-GRADE
Narayan	B-PERSON_NAME
Sundaram	I-PERSON_NAME
Subex	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Banswada	B-LOCATION
Toyota	B-CLIENT
Master	B-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Management	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Com	B-DEGREE
(Accounting)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Redundancy	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
IFMR	B-INSTITUTION
Graduate	I-INSTITUTION
School	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Business	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
92.0%	B-GRADE
Vivek	B-PERSON_NAME
Patil	I-PERSON_NAME
The	B-COMPANY
Man	I-COMPANY
Company	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ramban	B-LOCATION
Vicco	B-CLIENT
Laboratories	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
SDET	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
SHRM-SCP	B-DEGREE
–	O
Technical	B-FIELD
Debt	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
KJ	B-INSTITUTION
Somaiya	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
65.8%	B-GRADE
Oormila	B-PERSON_NAME
Bose	I-PERSON_NAME
Patriot	B-COMPANY
Memory	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Chhindwara	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Motilal	B-CLIENT
Oswal	I-CLIENT
Internal	B-ROLE
Tools	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Apr	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Quantum	I-DEGREE
Computing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Semantic	B-FIELD
Web	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Sri	B-INSTITUTION
Venkateswara	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
69.5%	B-GRADE
Sabha	B-PERSON_NAME
Ghosh	I-PERSON_NAME
Grafana	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
L&T	B-LOCATION
Infocity	I-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
Ambev	B-CLIENT
Automation	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Digital	I-DEGREE
Media)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Code	B-FIELD
Review	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Northeastern	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.0/10	B-GRADE
Snehlata	B-PERSON_NAME
Chandrasekhar	I-PERSON_NAME
Endress+Hauser	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Tiruchirapalli	B-LOCATION
Digit	B-CLIENT
Insurance	I-CLIENT
Julia	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Print	I-DEGREE
Tech)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Rubber	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
75.4%	B-GRADE
Sanjay	B-PERSON_NAME
Shukla	I-PERSON_NAME
Kingston	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Aundh	B-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
Nestle	B-CLIENT
BI	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Mathematics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Boosting	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Cornell	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
88.3%	B-GRADE
Anshuman	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyer	I-PERSON_NAME
Porter	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Tumakuru	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
Swiss	B-CLIENT
Re	I-CLIENT
Dynamics	B-ROLE
CRM	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Food	I-DEGREE
Technology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Predictive	B-FIELD
Maintenance	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Edinburgh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
55.7%	B-GRADE
Geeta	B-PERSON_NAME
Gaikwad	I-PERSON_NAME
Sitel	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Perungudi	B-LOCATION
Chennai	I-LOCATION
America	B-CLIENT
Movil	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
ServiceNow	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
August	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Social	I-DEGREE
Media)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Paint	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Rajasthan	B-INSTITUTION
Technical	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.0/10	B-GRADE
Nilay	B-PERSON_NAME
Saxena	I-PERSON_NAME
SimSim	B-COMPANY
Commerce	I-COMPANY
e,	O
Vasco	B-LOCATION
da	I-LOCATION
Gama	I-LOCATION
a	O
Mobikwik	B-CLIENT
Robotics	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Bioinformatics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Misinformation	B-FIELD
Detection	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Professor	B-INSTITUTION
Jayashankar	I-INSTITUTION
Telangana	I-INSTITUTION
State	I-INSTITUTION
Agricultural	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.5/10	B-GRADE
Vinita	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Swiggy	B-COMPANY
,	O
Mira	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Coal	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
SDET	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
BBA	B-DEGREE
(HR)	I-DEGREE
–	O
NFC	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Dharwad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.2/10	B-GRADE
Swapnil	B-PERSON_NAME
Malik	I-PERSON_NAME
Zoho	B-COMPANY
Books	I-COMPANY
,	O
Connaught	B-LOCATION
Place	I-LOCATION
Delhi	I-LOCATION
Aditya	B-CLIENT
Birla	I-CLIENT
Salesforce	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Material	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Watermarking	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
DTU	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.6/10	B-GRADE
Alpesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Ahmed	I-PERSON_NAME
Konstant	B-COMPANY
Infosolutions	I-COMPANY
,	O
RMZ	B-LOCATION
Nexity	I-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
Maybelline	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Load	B-ROLE
Balancer	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
February	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Mechatronics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Content	B-FIELD
Delivery	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Veer	B-INSTITUTION
Narmad	I-INSTITUTION
South	I-INSTITUTION
Gujarat	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.2/10	B-GRADE
Vinod	B-PERSON_NAME
Shukla	I-PERSON_NAME
Kellton	B-COMPANY
Tech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Tadipatri	B-LOCATION
Continental	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
UC	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
September	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Ayurveda)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Cold	B-FIELD
Chain	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Central	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Haryana	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.3/10	B-GRADE
Rupinder	B-PERSON_NAME
Banerjee	I-PERSON_NAME
i2iFunding	B-COMPANY
g,	O
Thiruvananthapuram	B-LOCATION
m	O
Liberty	B-CLIENT
Shoes	I-CLIENT
Identity	B-ROLE
&	I-ROLE
Access	I-ROLE
Management	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Geriatric	I-DEGREE
Care)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Supply	B-FIELD
Chain	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Narula	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
81.6%	B-GRADE
Bhagyashree	B-PERSON_NAME
Pawar	I-PERSON_NAME
Arm	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Bogadi	B-LOCATION
Mysore	I-LOCATION
Mphasis	B-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
UI	I-ROLE
Designer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(MLT)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Search	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Southern	I-INSTITUTION
California	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
86.0%	B-GRADE
Harshala	B-PERSON_NAME
Abraham	I-PERSON_NAME
ABB	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Salem	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Lotus	B-CLIENT
Herbals	I-CLIENT
Incident	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
B.Arch.	B-DEGREE
(Landscape)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Database	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
Central	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
South	I-INSTITUTION
Bihar	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
80.3%	B-GRADE
Chaturbhuj	B-PERSON_NAME
Wagh	I-PERSON_NAME
SleepyCat	B-COMPANY
t,	O
Haveri	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
l	O
Bounce	B-CLIENT
Infinity	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Mobile	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
MBA	B-DEGREE
(Business	I-DEGREE
Analytics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Instruction	B-FIELD
Tuning	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Pennsylvania	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.3/10	B-GRADE
Premila	B-PERSON_NAME
Rawat	I-PERSON_NAME
Codility	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Naroda	B-LOCATION
Ahmedabad	I-LOCATION
Parker	B-CLIENT
Hannifin	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Database	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Forestry)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Thermal	B-FIELD
Analysis	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Kumaraguru	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.5/10	B-GRADE
Ranajit	B-PERSON_NAME
Shah	I-PERSON_NAME
Cornerstone	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Cuttack	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
L'Oreal	B-CLIENT
API	B-ROLE
Tester	I-ROLE
June	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Certificate	B-DEGREE
(Sports	I-DEGREE
Nutrition)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Smart	B-FIELD
City	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Sathyabama	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Science	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.8/10	B-GRADE
Sannidhi	B-PERSON_NAME
Thomas	I-PERSON_NAME
Arya.ai	B-COMPANY
,	O
Ajmer	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Nokia	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Professional	B-ROLE
Services	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Combinatorics	B-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hamirpur	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
69.5%	B-GRADE
Ulka	B-PERSON_NAME
Tomar	I-PERSON_NAME
Zomato	B-COMPANY
,	O
Kanker	B-LOCATION
Info	B-CLIENT
Edge	I-CLIENT
L1	B-ROLE
Support	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
MBA	B-DEGREE
(Aviation	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Software	B-FIELD
Reuse	I-FIELD
,	O
National	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Pharmaceutical	I-INSTITUTION
Education	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Research	I-INSTITUTION
Mohali	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.6/10	B-GRADE
Deepthi	B-PERSON_NAME
Shukla	I-PERSON_NAME
iD	B-COMPANY
Fresh	I-COMPANY
Food	I-COMPANY
d,	O
Dwaraka	B-LOCATION
Nagar	I-LOCATION
Visakhapatnam	I-LOCATION
m	O
NEC	B-CLIENT
Assembly	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.P.P.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Neuromorphic	B-FIELD
Computing	I-FIELD
,	O
Kyoto	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.2/10	B-GRADE
Kritika	B-PERSON_NAME
Pawar	I-PERSON_NAME
DRS	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Wagholi	B-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
Adidas	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Incident	B-ROLE
Response	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
(French)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Generative	B-FIELD
AI	I-FIELD
,	O
Nanyang	B-INSTITUTION
Technological	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
61.2%	B-GRADE
Pramod	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhatt	I-PERSON_NAME
Minimalist	B-COMPANY
,	O
First	B-LOCATION
International	I-LOCATION
Financial	I-LOCATION
Centre	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Angel	B-CLIENT
Broking	I-CLIENT
Tier	B-ROLE
1	I-ROLE
SOC	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Psychology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Software	B-FIELD
Verification	I-FIELD
,	O
United	B-INSTITUTION
Arab	I-INSTITUTION
Emirates	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
61.8%	B-GRADE
Naresh	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhat	I-PERSON_NAME
Knowlarity	B-COMPANY
,	O
Gadag	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
Syngene	B-CLIENT
International	I-CLIENT
BI	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Apr	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Anthropology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Industrial	B-FIELD
IoT	I-FIELD
T,	O
Uttarakhand	B-INSTITUTION
Technical	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
y,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
0,	O
9.7/10	B-GRADE
0	O
Nidhi	B-PERSON_NAME
Dubey	I-PERSON_NAME
Milkbasket	B-COMPANY
,	O
Howrah	B-LOCATION
ABB	B-CLIENT
Group	I-CLIENT
Statistician	B-ROLE
June	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
BBA	B-DEGREE
(Online)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Supervised	B-FIELD
Learning	I-FIELD
,	O
UIET	B-INSTITUTION
Chandigarh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.5/10	B-GRADE
Indrajit	B-PERSON_NAME
Begum	I-PERSON_NAME
Truecaller	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Gift	B-LOCATION
City	I-LOCATION
Gandhinagar	I-LOCATION
Zandu	B-CLIENT
Pharma	I-CLIENT
Infrastructure	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
(Broadcasting)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Aided	I-FIELD
Manufacturing	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Sri	I-INSTITUTION
City	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.3/10	B-GRADE
Manoja	B-PERSON_NAME
Jadhav	I-PERSON_NAME
CSS	B-COMPANY
Corp	I-COMPANY
,	O
LB	B-LOCATION
Nagar	I-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
BSNL	B-CLIENT
Mobile	I-CLIENT
VP	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Engineering	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Horticulture)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Innovation	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Florida	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.4/10	B-GRADE
Paresh	B-PERSON_NAME
Balasubramanian	I-PERSON_NAME
Ultrahuman	B-COMPANY
,	O
Avinashi	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Coimbatore	I-LOCATION
Fortis	B-CLIENT
Healthcare	I-CLIENT
Software	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Tourism	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Environmental	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIM	B-INSTITUTION
Indore	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
90.8%	B-GRADE
Ashima	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Webkul	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sector	B-LOCATION
16	I-LOCATION
Noida	I-LOCATION
Regal	B-CLIENT
Beloit	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Tier	B-ROLE
3	I-ROLE
SOC	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Apr	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Blockchain)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Collaborative	B-FIELD
Manufacturing	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
CMR	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.0/10	B-GRADE
Dibyendu	B-PERSON_NAME
Dey	I-PERSON_NAME
ConfirmTkt	B-COMPANY
t,	O
Mindspace	B-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
d	O
Jio	B-CLIENT
Phone	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Release	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Sep	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Finance	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Business	B-FIELD
Process	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Tsinghua	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
76.8%	B-GRADE
Yashoda	B-PERSON_NAME
Agarwal	I-PERSON_NAME
Cashfree	B-COMPANY
Payments	I-COMPANY
,	O
Gulbarga	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
BHP	B-CLIENT
5G	B-ROLE
Network	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
BPOD	B-DEGREE
–	O
Social	B-FIELD
Network	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIM	B-INSTITUTION
Visakhapatnam	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
80.4%	B-GRADE
Krishnamurthy	B-PERSON_NAME
Naik	I-PERSON_NAME
BEML	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Chatra	B-LOCATION
Seagate	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Data	B-ROLE
Governance	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
June	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Public	I-DEGREE
Admin)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Robotics	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
Jai	B-INSTITUTION
Narain	I-INSTITUTION
Vyas	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
61.8%	B-GRADE
Indu	B-PERSON_NAME
Tomar	I-PERSON_NAME
TCI	B-COMPANY
Express	I-COMPANY
,	O
Rajsamand	B-LOCATION
Lava	B-CLIENT
International	I-CLIENT
Groovy	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
Google	B-DEGREE
Cloud	I-DEGREE
Certified	I-DEGREE
–	O
Agricultural	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
Future	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Management	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
61.3%	B-GRADE
Bhavita	B-PERSON_NAME
Ghosh	I-PERSON_NAME
Plantix	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
One	B-LOCATION
Indiabulls	I-LOCATION
Centre	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
ETV	B-CLIENT
Telugu	I-CLIENT
Self-Driving	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Broadcasting)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Industrial	B-FIELD
IoT	I-FIELD
T,	O
IGDTUW	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
i,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
3,	O
9.8/10	B-GRADE
0	O
Jatin	B-PERSON_NAME
Ahmed	I-PERSON_NAME
MX	B-COMPANY
TakaTak	I-COMPANY
k,	O
Latehar	B-LOCATION
r	O
SK	B-CLIENT
Hynix	I-CLIENT
Node.js	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Machine	I-DEGREE
Learning)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Sentiment	B-FIELD
Analysis	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
GL	B-INSTITUTION
Bajaj	I-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.1/10	B-GRADE
Dilip	B-PERSON_NAME
Desai	I-PERSON_NAME
Amazon	B-COMPANY
Music	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Gopeshwar	B-LOCATION
Norgren	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Associate	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Distance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Data	B-FIELD
Protection	I-FIELD
,	O
Sido	B-INSTITUTION
Kanhu	I-INSTITUTION
Murmu	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.5/10	B-GRADE
Vijayashree	B-PERSON_NAME
Natarajan	I-PERSON_NAME
DTDC	B-COMPANY
Courier	I-COMPANY
,	O
Berhampur	B-LOCATION
Sugar	B-CLIENT
Cosmetics	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
ML	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
B.J.M.C.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Computational	B-FIELD
Economics	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Dhanbad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.2/10	B-GRADE
Parveen	B-PERSON_NAME
Bains	I-PERSON_NAME
Rapid7	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sirohi	B-LOCATION
Daikin	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Technical	B-ROLE
Writer	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Tax	I-DEGREE
Law)	I-DEGREE
–	O
AI	B-FIELD
Fairness	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Panimalar	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.4/10	B-GRADE
Aditya	B-PERSON_NAME
Roy	I-PERSON_NAME
Moj	B-COMPANY
,	O
Kota	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
IRDA	B-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
January	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Dec	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Travel	I-DEGREE
&	I-DEGREE
Tourism)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Sonar	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
Somaiya	B-INSTITUTION
Vidyavihar	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
72.8%	B-GRADE
Abhinandan	B-PERSON_NAME
Pawar	I-PERSON_NAME
GalaxEye	B-COMPANY
e,	O
Arrah	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Adani	B-CLIENT
Group	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
API	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Economics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Text	B-FIELD
Mining	I-FIELD
,	O
National	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Pharmaceutical	I-INSTITUTION
Education	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Research	I-INSTITUTION
Mohali	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
59.3%	B-GRADE
Chitra	B-PERSON_NAME
Menon	I-PERSON_NAME
Times	B-COMPANY
Internet	I-COMPANY
,	O
Mira	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Fujikura	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
jQuery	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
May	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(CE)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Information	B-FIELD
Security	I-FIELD
,	O
Cornell	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
70.0%	B-GRADE
Mausami	B-PERSON_NAME
Singh	I-PERSON_NAME
Sonata	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
,	O
Tambaram	B-LOCATION
Chennai	I-LOCATION
Hypermarket	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
IT	B-ROLE
Business	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Textile	I-DEGREE
Design)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Genetic	B-FIELD
Algorithms	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Michigan	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.4/10	B-GRADE
Joydeep	B-PERSON_NAME
Siddiqui	I-PERSON_NAME
Newton	B-COMPANY
School	I-COMPANY
,	O
Androth	B-LOCATION
DEN	B-CLIENT
Networks	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Frontend	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Cyber	I-DEGREE
Security)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Edge	B-FIELD
Computing	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Warangal	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
61.6%	B-GRADE
Jayashree	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhat	I-PERSON_NAME
Observe.AI	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Hardoi	B-LOCATION
Birla	B-CLIENT
Corporation	I-CLIENT
Site	B-ROLE
Reliability	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Anaesthesia)	I-DEGREE
–	O
M-Commerce	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Silchar	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.5/10	B-GRADE
Anjana	B-PERSON_NAME
Raheem	I-PERSON_NAME
iMerit	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
y,	O
Tiruchirapalli	B-LOCATION
i	O
Cholamandalam	B-CLIENT
Finance	I-CLIENT
Lakehouse	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Hotel	I-DEGREE
Management)	I-DEGREE
–	O
RLHF	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Aditya	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
83.6%	B-GRADE
Charulata	B-PERSON_NAME
Shah	I-PERSON_NAME
Rupifi	B-COMPANY
,	O
Rae	B-LOCATION
Bareli	I-LOCATION
Zepto	B-CLIENT
Commerce	I-CLIENT
Network	B-ROLE
Security	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.P.Ed.	B-DEGREE
–	O
OLAP	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Guru	B-INSTITUTION
Ghasidas	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.8/10	B-GRADE
Irshad	B-PERSON_NAME
Rawat	I-PERSON_NAME
Kellton	B-COMPANY
Tech	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
,	O
Malappuram	B-LOCATION
Adani	B-CLIENT
Solar	I-CLIENT
SAP	B-ROLE
HANA	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Feb	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(PR)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Steganography	B-FIELD
,	O
MIT	B-INSTITUTION
World	I-INSTITUTION
Peace	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
76.9%	B-GRADE
Ram	B-PERSON_NAME
Tomar	I-PERSON_NAME
GoComet	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Kupwara	B-LOCATION
a	O
Parker	B-CLIENT
Hannifin	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
FastAPI	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
August	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
MPT	B-DEGREE
–	O
Medical	B-FIELD
Electronics	I-FIELD
,	O
ETH	B-INSTITUTION
Zurich	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
55.5%	B-GRADE
Himanshi	B-PERSON_NAME
Wagh	I-PERSON_NAME
PayU	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Daporijo	B-LOCATION
o	O
Eicher	B-CLIENT
Motors	I-CLIENT
ServiceNow	B-ROLE
ITSM	I-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
t	O
November	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(PR)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Cloud	B-FIELD
Security	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.5/10	B-GRADE
Renu	B-PERSON_NAME
Mishra	I-PERSON_NAME
QBurst	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sanguem	B-LOCATION
Vikram	B-CLIENT
Solar	I-CLIENT
Virtualization	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Anaesthesia)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Database	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Punjab	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
Chandigarh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.6/10	B-GRADE
Vaishali	B-PERSON_NAME
More	I-PERSON_NAME
PharmEasy	B-COMPANY
y,	O
Uttara	B-LOCATION
Kannada	I-LOCATION
a	O
Balkrishna	B-CLIENT
Industries	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Design	I-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
BPT	B-DEGREE
–	O
Digital	B-FIELD
Rights	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
NIPER	B-INSTITUTION
Guwahati	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.2%	B-GRADE
Brindaban	B-PERSON_NAME
Roy	I-PERSON_NAME
Darktrace	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Bannerghatta	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Bangalore	I-LOCATION
Axis	B-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
Flink	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(SEO)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Conversational	B-FIELD
AI	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Melbourne	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.4/10	B-GRADE
Sagarika	B-PERSON_NAME
Sen	I-PERSON_NAME
BankBazaar	B-COMPANY
r,	O
Maninagar	B-LOCATION
Ahmedabad	I-LOCATION
d	O
ADNOC	B-CLIENT
Production	B-ROLE
Support	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
January	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
CS	B-DEGREE
(Company	I-DEGREE
Secretary)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Prosthetics	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Kolhan	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
79.0%	B-GRADE
Mohit	B-PERSON_NAME
Wagh	I-PERSON_NAME
Quikr	B-COMPANY
,	O
Kolshet	B-LOCATION
Thane	I-LOCATION
Ola	B-CLIENT
Cabs	I-CLIENT
QA	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
October	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Fisheries)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Banking	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Calcutta	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.7/10	B-GRADE
Gulshan	B-PERSON_NAME
Banerjee	I-PERSON_NAME
Chingari	B-COMPANY
,	O
Haveri	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
Cognizant	B-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Frontend	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
+	I-DEGREE
M.A.	I-DEGREE
(Integrated)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Collision	B-FIELD
Avoidance	I-FIELD
,	O
Hemchandracharya	B-INSTITUTION
North	I-INSTITUTION
Gujarat	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.7/10	B-GRADE
Kulwant	B-PERSON_NAME
Mathew	I-PERSON_NAME
Cornerstone	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Patiala	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Blinkit	B-CLIENT
Perl	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Lib	B-DEGREE
(Information	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Environmental	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Alliance	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
81.3%	B-GRADE
Avika	B-PERSON_NAME
Chaudhary	I-PERSON_NAME
BEL	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Budgam	B-LOCATION
Sharda	B-CLIENT
Motor	I-CLIENT
Developer	B-ROLE
Relations	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Animal	I-DEGREE
Husbandry)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Access	B-FIELD
Control	I-FIELD
,	O
IISc	B-INSTITUTION
Bangalore	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
94.4%	B-GRADE
Natarajan	B-PERSON_NAME
Rajagopalan	I-PERSON_NAME
Byju's	B-COMPANY
,	O
Malda	B-LOCATION
Tata	B-CLIENT
Elxsi	I-CLIENT
Incident	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
November	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
M.Mus.	B-DEGREE
(Music	I-DEGREE
Technology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Paint	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
KJ	B-INSTITUTION
Somaiya	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
75.6%	B-GRADE
Meena	B-PERSON_NAME
Das	I-PERSON_NAME
Sphinx	B-COMPANY
Worldbiz	I-COMPANY
,	O
Rewa	B-LOCATION
Delhivery	B-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Backend	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Metallurgy)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Optoelectronics	B-FIELD
,	O
New	B-INSTITUTION
Horizon	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
91.5%	B-GRADE
Siddhesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhat	I-PERSON_NAME
Focus	B-COMPANY
Softnet	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Belapur	B-LOCATION
Navi	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Al	B-CLIENT
Rajhi	I-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
Process	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
June	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Fashion	I-DEGREE
Designing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Cyber	B-FIELD
Security	I-FIELD
,	O
Nagaland	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
73.5%	B-GRADE
Nikunj	B-PERSON_NAME
Chauhan	I-PERSON_NAME
Mettler-Toledo	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Nellore	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Ravin	B-CLIENT
Cables	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Release	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
June	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
M.E.	B-DEGREE
(Power	I-DEGREE
Systems)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Federated	B-FIELD
Learning	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Surathkal	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
63.8%	B-GRADE
Medha	B-PERSON_NAME
Reddy	I-PERSON_NAME
Porter	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Harda	B-LOCATION
Restaurant	B-CLIENT
Brands	I-CLIENT
Asia	I-CLIENT
GraphQL	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
September	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Nano	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Digital	B-FIELD
Asset	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
NIFT	B-INSTITUTION
Mumbai	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.5/10	B-GRADE
Genevieve	B-PERSON_NAME
Pawar	I-PERSON_NAME
PhonePe	B-COMPANY
e,	O
Wayanad	B-LOCATION
d	O
Ericsson	B-CLIENT
IT	B-ROLE
Program	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
BCL	B-DEGREE
–	O
Sparse	B-FIELD
Retrieval	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
ICFAI	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.4%	B-GRADE
Tejas	B-PERSON_NAME
Agarwal	I-PERSON_NAME
MapmyIndia	B-COMPANY
a,	O
Balaghat	B-LOCATION
t	O
Inditex	B-CLIENT
DevRel	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
r	O
October	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Import	I-DEGREE
Export)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Antenna	B-FIELD
Design	I-FIELD
,	O
Institute	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Management	I-INSTITUTION
Kolkata	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
93.8%	B-GRADE
Kamini	B-PERSON_NAME
Tiwari	I-PERSON_NAME
Apna	B-COMPANY
,	O
Thiruvananthapuram	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
VKC	B-CLIENT
Group	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
UX	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Virtual	I-DEGREE
Reality)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Redundant	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Goa	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.3/10	B-GRADE
Shweta	B-PERSON_NAME
Mishra	I-PERSON_NAME
Axio	B-COMPANY
(Capital	I-COMPANY
Float)	I-COMPANY
,	O
Bandipora	B-LOCATION
Maersk	B-CLIENT
Group	B-ROLE
Product	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Feb	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Mining)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Fuzzing	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Ohio	B-INSTITUTION
State	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.1/10	B-GRADE
Damodar	B-PERSON_NAME
Tomar	I-PERSON_NAME
Cropin	B-COMPANY
SmartFarm	I-COMPANY
m,	O
Purulia	B-LOCATION
a	O
Norgren	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Azure	B-ROLE
Solutions	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
June	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Forestry)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Hardware	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
JIPMER	B-INSTITUTION
Puducherry	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.8/10	B-GRADE
Anju	B-PERSON_NAME
Singh	I-PERSON_NAME
Brocade	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Jabalpur	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Metro	B-CLIENT
Shoes	I-CLIENT
Engineering	B-ROLE
Fellow	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Tourism)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Software	B-FIELD
Reuse	I-FIELD
,	O
Maharshi	B-INSTITUTION
Dayanand	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
87.9%	B-GRADE
Charu	B-PERSON_NAME
Mehta	I-PERSON_NAME
Ignitho	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
My	B-LOCATION
Home	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
Just	B-CLIENT
Herbs	I-CLIENT
Distributed	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Editing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
MEMS	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
CMR	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.6/10	B-GRADE
Jaspreet	B-PERSON_NAME
Joshi	I-PERSON_NAME
IntouchCX	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Aurangabad	B-LOCATION
Bihar	I-LOCATION
r	O
Eaton	B-CLIENT
Electrical	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Industrial	B-ROLE
Automation	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
October	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Child	I-DEGREE
Psychology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Advertising	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Netaji	B-INSTITUTION
Subhas	I-INSTITUTION
Open	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
68.9%	B-GRADE
Joydip	B-PERSON_NAME
Raheem	I-PERSON_NAME
Gradeup	B-COMPANY
(BYJU's	I-COMPANY
Exam	I-COMPANY
Prep)	I-COMPANY
,	O
Scheme	B-LOCATION
78	I-LOCATION
Indore	I-LOCATION
Kotak	B-CLIENT
Mahindra	I-CLIENT
Sales	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(IP	I-DEGREE
Law)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Message	B-FIELD
Queuing	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Lund	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
82.6%	B-GRADE
Zeenat	B-PERSON_NAME
Joshi	I-PERSON_NAME
Trigent	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
,	O
Arrah	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
AGL	B-CLIENT
Energy	I-CLIENT
Staff	B-ROLE
Security	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Applied	I-DEGREE
Mathematics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Pair	B-FIELD
Programming	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Florida	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.1/10	B-GRADE
Kartik	B-PERSON_NAME
Chauhan	I-PERSON_NAME
Sigmoid	B-COMPANY
Analytics	I-COMPANY
,	O
Jabalpur	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Glenmark	B-CLIENT
Pharma	I-CLIENT
Technical	B-ROLE
Evangelist	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Mining)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Full	B-FIELD
Stack	I-FIELD
Development	I-FIELD
,	O
Aditya	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.2%	B-GRADE
Mrinalini	B-PERSON_NAME
Pillai	I-PERSON_NAME
Wealthy.in	B-COMPANY
,	O
Khargone	B-LOCATION
Khadi	B-CLIENT
Natural	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
IoT	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
November	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Economics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Low	B-FIELD
Code	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Pune	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
62.8%	B-GRADE
Bilal	B-PERSON_NAME
Irfan	I-PERSON_NAME
Seagate	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Hamirpur	B-LOCATION
HP	I-LOCATION
Thyrocare	B-CLIENT
PCB	B-ROLE
Design	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Computational	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Plagiarism	B-FIELD
Detection	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
MAIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.5/10	B-GRADE
Dibyendu	B-PERSON_NAME
Dey	I-PERSON_NAME
BroadSoft	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Wagholi	B-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
e	O
Nokia	B-CLIENT
PowerShell	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
May	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
M.Des.	B-DEGREE
(Graphic)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Research	B-FIELD
Data	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Hemvati	B-INSTITUTION
Nandan	I-INSTITUTION
Bahuguna	I-INSTITUTION
Garhwal	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.5/10	B-GRADE
Anitha	B-PERSON_NAME
Shah	I-PERSON_NAME
InstaSafe	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Tiruchirapalli	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Axis	B-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Technical	I-ROLE
Writer	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
M.Pharm	B-DEGREE
–	O
Caching	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Sambalpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.4/10	B-GRADE
Vanita	B-PERSON_NAME
Krishnan	I-PERSON_NAME
Mylab	B-COMPANY
Discovery	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
,	O
Varanasi	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Qatar	B-CLIENT
National	I-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Agile	I-ROLE
Coach	I-ROLE
August	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Taxation)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Innovation	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
SPA	B-INSTITUTION
Vijayawada	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
57.8%	B-GRADE
Pragnya	B-PERSON_NAME
George	I-PERSON_NAME
Workday	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Mansa	B-LOCATION
JNPT	B-CLIENT
Cybersecurity	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Ed.	B-DEGREE
–	O
NFC	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NLU	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
68.1%	B-GRADE
Nateshar	B-PERSON_NAME
Venkataraman	I-PERSON_NAME
Chetu	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Yellandu	B-LOCATION
Apar	B-CLIENT
Industries	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Program	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Construction	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Printing	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Monash	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.0/10	B-GRADE
Dipti	B-PERSON_NAME
Ramachandran	I-PERSON_NAME
BlackBuck	B-COMPANY
k,	O
Viman	B-LOCATION
Nagar	I-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
e	O
Amul	B-CLIENT
Security	B-ROLE
Automation	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Sports	I-DEGREE
Management)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Payment	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Gautam	B-INSTITUTION
Buddha	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.8/10	B-GRADE
Partha	B-PERSON_NAME
Sandhu	I-PERSON_NAME
Jupiter	B-COMPANY
Money	I-COMPANY
,	O
Panvel	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
Leonardo	B-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Salesforce	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
June	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
B.P.Ed.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Fuzzy	B-FIELD
Logic	I-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
Vinoba	B-INSTITUTION
Bhave	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.7/10	B-GRADE
Taposhree	B-PERSON_NAME
Mehta	I-PERSON_NAME
Hughes	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Purnia	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Dhanuka	B-CLIENT
Agritech	I-CLIENT
Business	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Gender	I-DEGREE
Studies)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Contrastive	B-FIELD
Learning	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Professor	B-INSTITUTION
Jayashankar	I-INSTITUTION
Telangana	I-INSTITUTION
State	I-INSTITUTION
Agricultural	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.2/10	B-GRADE
Manas	B-PERSON_NAME
Singh	I-PERSON_NAME
RipenApps	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Avadi	B-LOCATION
Chennai	I-LOCATION
i	O
Sea	B-CLIENT
Limited	I-CLIENT
Design	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Jewellery	I-DEGREE
Design)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Algorithm	B-FIELD
Design	I-FIELD
,	O
Academy	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
Hooghly	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
57.6%	B-GRADE
Jaswant	B-PERSON_NAME
Abraham	I-PERSON_NAME
ZEE5	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Cuttack	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Malabar	B-CLIENT
Gold	I-CLIENT
API	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Plant	I-DEGREE
Breeding)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Dialogue	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
BMS	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
94.4%	B-GRADE
Elanchezhian	B-PERSON_NAME
Chauhan	I-PERSON_NAME
Veeam	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sivaganga	B-LOCATION
Big	B-CLIENT
C	I-CLIENT
Mobiles	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
BI	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
MS	B-DEGREE
(Surgery)	I-DEGREE
–	O
GreenTech	B-FIELD
h,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Dharwad	I-INSTITUTION
d,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
4,	O
7.3/10	B-GRADE
0	O
Deepak	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyer	I-PERSON_NAME
Masters	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
GST	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ponda	B-LOCATION
Cochin	B-CLIENT
Shipyard	I-CLIENT
Infrastructure	B-ROLE
as	I-ROLE
Code	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Graphic	I-DEGREE
Design)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Non-Destructive	B-FIELD
Testing	I-FIELD
,	O
Bennett	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
70.3%	B-GRADE
Narendra	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Pratt	B-COMPANY
&	I-COMPANY
Whitney	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Shahjahanpur	B-LOCATION
Vijay	B-CLIENT
Sales	I-CLIENT
Godot	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
November	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Corporate	I-DEGREE
Law)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Microelectronics	B-FIELD
,	O
Qatar	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.2/10	B-GRADE
Krishnendu	B-PERSON_NAME
Sheikh	I-PERSON_NAME
Salesforce	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ratlam	B-LOCATION
Hindalco	B-CLIENT
Novelis	I-CLIENT
Wireless	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Quantum	I-DEGREE
Computing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Rapid	B-FIELD
Application	I-FIELD
Development	I-FIELD
,	O
Sathyabama	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Science	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.7%	B-GRADE
Yashpal	B-PERSON_NAME
Srivastava	I-PERSON_NAME
Tenable	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Alibag	B-LOCATION
Panasonic	B-CLIENT
Healthtech	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Pharmacy)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Irony	B-FIELD
Detection	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Wisconsin	I-INSTITUTION
Madison	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.5/10	B-GRADE
Uday	B-PERSON_NAME
Pandey	I-PERSON_NAME
Emerson	B-COMPANY
Electric	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Dharwad	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Roche	B-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Embedded	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
B.F.A.	B-DEGREE
(Photography)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Electronics	B-FIELD
,	O
Plaksha	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
80.0%	B-GRADE
Prashant	B-PERSON_NAME
More	I-PERSON_NAME
WNS	B-COMPANY
Global	I-COMPANY
Services	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kharadi	B-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
Texmaco	B-CLIENT
Rail	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Program	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Mus.	B-DEGREE
(Western)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Data	B-FIELD
Lake	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bangalore	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.1/10	B-GRADE
Chhaya	B-PERSON_NAME
Jadhav	I-PERSON_NAME
IBM	B-COMPANY
QRadar	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Goregaon	B-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Inditex	B-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
UX	I-ROLE
Researcher	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
BBA	B-DEGREE
(Marketing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Innovation	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Bangalore	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.6/10	B-GRADE
Mithun	B-PERSON_NAME
Shah	I-PERSON_NAME
GE	B-COMPANY
Aviation	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Suptapur	B-LOCATION
Serum	B-CLIENT
Institute	I-CLIENT
Telecommunications	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Metaverse)	I-DEGREE
–	O
ECE	B-FIELD
,	O
Mar	B-INSTITUTION
Athanasius	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.2/10	B-GRADE
Jayaraman	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Thermo	B-COMPANY
Fisher	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Khunti	B-LOCATION
ManipalCigna	B-CLIENT
a	O
ServiceNow	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
t	O
May	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Biotechnology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Industrial	B-FIELD
IoT	I-FIELD
T,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Washington	I-INSTITUTION
n,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
9,	O
8.6/10	B-GRADE
0	O
Farida	B-PERSON_NAME
Shukla	I-PERSON_NAME
Udaan	B-COMPANY
,	O
NIMZ	B-LOCATION
Prakasam	I-LOCATION
AstraZeneca	B-CLIENT
a	O
Digital	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Broadcasting)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Applications	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Leeds	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.2/10	B-GRADE
Deependra	B-PERSON_NAME
Chaudhary	I-PERSON_NAME
Subex	B-COMPANY
Limited	I-COMPANY
,	O
Lonavala	B-LOCATION
GTBank	B-CLIENT
Serverless	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
January	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
CA	B-DEGREE
(Chartered	I-DEGREE
Accountant)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Key-Value	B-FIELD
Store	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Raghu	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.9/10	B-GRADE
Shrinivas	B-PERSON_NAME
Mehta	I-PERSON_NAME
mCaffeine	B-COMPANY
e,	O
Kannur	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
l	O
Hindustan	B-CLIENT
Copper	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Unity	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Drone	I-DEGREE
Technology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Sparse	B-FIELD
Retrieval	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
BVRIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
86.3%	B-GRADE
Harini	B-PERSON_NAME
Singh	I-PERSON_NAME
Talent500	B-COMPANY
,	O
Leh	B-LOCATION
Airtel	B-CLIENT
Africa	I-CLIENT
GCP	B-ROLE
Solutions	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
January	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Applied	I-DEGREE
Mathematics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Human	B-FIELD
Resource	I-FIELD
Information	I-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
Amity	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.6/10	B-GRADE
Minakshi	B-PERSON_NAME
Menon	I-PERSON_NAME
Inshorts	B-COMPANY
,	O
Delhi	B-LOCATION
Glenmark	B-CLIENT
Pharma	I-CLIENT
Staff	B-ROLE
Frontend	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Social	I-DEGREE
Work)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Software	B-FIELD
Verification	I-FIELD
,	O
IGDTUW	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.2/10	B-GRADE
Subarna	B-PERSON_NAME
Agarwal	I-PERSON_NAME
Fasal	B-COMPANY
,	O
Ayodhya	B-LOCATION
FDC	B-CLIENT
Limited	I-CLIENT
Game	B-ROLE
Tester	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
October	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
M.H.M.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Intent	B-FIELD
Recognition	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
AFMC	B-INSTITUTION
Pune	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
57.2%	B-GRADE
Anish	B-PERSON_NAME
Rawat	I-PERSON_NAME
Shop101	B-COMPANY
,	O
SR	B-LOCATION
Nagar	I-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
NIIT	B-CLIENT
Technologies	I-CLIENT
Data	B-ROLE
Warehouse	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
DNB	B-DEGREE
–	O
Graph	B-FIELD
Theory	I-FIELD
,	O
Dr	B-INSTITUTION
YSR	I-INSTITUTION
Horticultural	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
74.4%	B-GRADE
Uttara	B-PERSON_NAME
Nair	I-PERSON_NAME
Hasura	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ambikapur	B-LOCATION
Exide	B-CLIENT
Industries	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Solution	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Sep	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
MD	B-DEGREE
–	O
Thermal	B-FIELD
Analysis	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Cummins	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
Pune	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.7/10	B-GRADE
Jatinder	B-PERSON_NAME
Verma	I-PERSON_NAME
Queppelin	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kallakurichi	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Zee	B-CLIENT
Kannada	I-CLIENT
Reporting	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Web	I-DEGREE
Technology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Redundancy	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Goa	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
78.5%	B-GRADE
Uma	B-PERSON_NAME
Rawat	I-PERSON_NAME
Fisdom	B-COMPANY
,	O
Sector	B-LOCATION
44	I-LOCATION
Gurugram	I-LOCATION
Garnier	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Chaos	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
September	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Editing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Audio	B-FIELD
Streaming	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Kolhan	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
71.5%	B-GRADE
Gowri	B-PERSON_NAME
Bose	I-PERSON_NAME
Capgemini	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Barmer	B-LOCATION
Air	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
API	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Health	I-DEGREE
Informatics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Haptics	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Birla	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
Mesra	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
59.3%	B-GRADE
Tejinder	B-PERSON_NAME
Jadhav	I-PERSON_NAME
Cult.fit	B-COMPANY
,	O
Bharuch	B-LOCATION
Eicher	B-CLIENT
Motors	I-CLIENT
Go	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
June	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
BBA	B-DEGREE
(Finance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
BioMEMS	B-FIELD
S,	O
Pt	B-INSTITUTION
Ravishankar	I-INSTITUTION
Shukla	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
y,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
7,	O
6.3/10	B-GRADE
0	O
Devasmita	B-PERSON_NAME
Shankar	I-PERSON_NAME
Unbxd	B-COMPANY
,	O
Allahabad	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
AU	B-CLIENT
Small	I-CLIENT
Finance	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
GCP	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Computational	I-DEGREE
Biology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Graphics	I-FIELD
,	O
Maharshi	B-INSTITUTION
Dayanand	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.2/10	B-GRADE
Mariappan	B-PERSON_NAME
Rawat	I-PERSON_NAME
Avaya	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Baran	B-LOCATION
Airbus	B-CLIENT
Group	I-CLIENT
Staff	B-ROLE
Product	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
B.Com	B-DEGREE
–	O
Leather	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Srinivas	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.6/10	B-GRADE
Yashpal	B-PERSON_NAME
Srivastava	I-PERSON_NAME
Medlife	B-COMPANY
,	O
Mussoorie	B-LOCATION
Eni	B-CLIENT
Mobile	B-ROLE
Product	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
BSN	B-DEGREE
–	O
Food	B-FIELD
Traceability	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Dayananda	B-INSTITUTION
Sagar	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.2/10	B-GRADE
Jayesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Malik	I-PERSON_NAME
ConveGenius	B-COMPANY
s,	O
Raigarh	B-LOCATION
h	O
Cera	B-CLIENT
Sanitaryware	I-CLIENT
UAT	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Apr	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Health	I-DEGREE
Informatics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Transportation	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Ranchi	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.3/10	B-GRADE
Rakhee	B-PERSON_NAME
Chandrasekhar	I-PERSON_NAME
NutritionistPro	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Amini	B-LOCATION
i	O
Neon	B-CLIENT
Laboratories	I-CLIENT
Web	B-ROLE
UI	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Applied	I-DEGREE
Chemistry)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Fire	B-FIELD
Detection	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
North	B-INSTITUTION
Eastern	I-INSTITUTION
Hill	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
87.4%	B-GRADE
Dhrupad	B-PERSON_NAME
Sundaram	I-PERSON_NAME
NetSuite	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Jigani	B-LOCATION
Bangalore	I-LOCATION
e	O
America	B-CLIENT
Movil	I-CLIENT
Platform	B-ROLE
Frontend	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Cyber	I-DEGREE
Security)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Human	B-FIELD
in	I-FIELD
the	I-FIELD
Loop	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Indian	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Petroleum	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Energy	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.7/10	B-GRADE
Rupa	B-PERSON_NAME
Chatterjee	I-PERSON_NAME
ThoughtSpot	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Jaisalmer	B-LOCATION
r	O
Reliance	B-CLIENT
Industries	I-CLIENT
Prompt	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Mechatronics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Knowledge	B-FIELD
Graph	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Indian	B-INSTITUTION
Maritime	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
64.7%	B-GRADE
Usha	B-PERSON_NAME
Kumar	I-PERSON_NAME
Cigniti	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Purba	B-LOCATION
Bardhaman	I-LOCATION
Allianz	B-CLIENT
Robotics	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
BBA	B-DEGREE
(Distance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Flood	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Tamil	B-INSTITUTION
Nadu	I-INSTITUTION
Agricultural	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.6/10	B-GRADE
Trisha	B-PERSON_NAME
Sen	I-PERSON_NAME
CronJ	B-COMPANY
IT	I-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Kota	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Electrolux	B-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Delivery	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Online)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Neural	B-FIELD
Networks	I-FIELD
,	O
Manipal	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.2/10	B-GRADE
Raghav	B-PERSON_NAME
Krishnan	I-PERSON_NAME
Elastic	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Techzone	B-LOCATION
Greater	I-LOCATION
Noida	I-LOCATION
Endress	B-CLIENT
Hauser	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
UI	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
M.Phil	B-DEGREE
(Library	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Space	B-FIELD
Robotics	I-FIELD
,	O
BIT	B-INSTITUTION
Sindri	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.1/10	B-GRADE
Jaspreet	B-PERSON_NAME
Joshi	I-PERSON_NAME
Indifi	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Nizamabad	B-LOCATION
Havells	B-CLIENT
Cables	I-CLIENT
Oracle	B-ROLE
Fusion	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
M.Com	B-DEGREE
(Business	I-DEGREE
Studies)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Transcoding	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Surathkal	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.3/10	B-GRADE
Vineet	B-PERSON_NAME
Saxena	I-PERSON_NAME
HackerEarth	B-COMPANY
h,	O
Rajahmundry	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Muthoot	B-CLIENT
Microfin	I-CLIENT
Objective-C	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
LL.M.	B-DEGREE
(Banking	I-DEGREE
Law)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Computational	B-FIELD
Fluid	I-FIELD
Dynamics	I-FIELD
,	O
NMIMS	B-INSTITUTION
Mumbai	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
70.0%	B-GRADE
Sucharita	B-PERSON_NAME
Saxena	I-PERSON_NAME
Mu	B-COMPANY
Sigma	I-COMPANY
,	O
Paschim	B-LOCATION
Bardhaman	I-LOCATION
Morepen	B-CLIENT
Labs	I-CLIENT
Staff	B-ROLE
ML	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
B.U.D.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Systems	B-FIELD
Biology	I-FIELD
,	O
Uppsala	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.7/10	B-GRADE
Dhruv	B-PERSON_NAME
Kulkarni	I-PERSON_NAME
Mercer	B-COMPANY
Mettl	I-COMPANY
,	O
Jodhpur	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Vestas	B-CLIENT
Wind	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Embedded	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
MBA	B-DEGREE
(Banking)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Emission	B-FIELD
Monitoring	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Pune	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
55.4%	B-GRADE
Anshika	B-PERSON_NAME
Gupta	I-PERSON_NAME
Okinawa	B-COMPANY
Autotech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Mulugu	B-LOCATION
ADNOC	B-CLIENT
VR	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Bio-informatics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Container	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Birla	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
Mesra	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
78.9%	B-GRADE
Rajkumar	B-PERSON_NAME
Das	I-PERSON_NAME
Puppet	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Navi	B-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
CBD	I-LOCATION
Belapur	I-LOCATION
Coromandel	B-CLIENT
International	I-CLIENT
Reporting	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Insurance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Scripting	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.3%	B-GRADE
Kundan	B-PERSON_NAME
Roy	I-PERSON_NAME
Josh	B-COMPANY
App	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sivakasi	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Swiggy	B-CLIENT
Stores	I-CLIENT
Product	B-ROLE
Intern	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Urban	I-DEGREE
Planning)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Decentralized	B-FIELD
Finance	I-FIELD
,	O
Rajiv	B-INSTITUTION
Gandhi	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
Arunachal	I-INSTITUTION
Pradesh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.3/10	B-GRADE
Anand	B-PERSON_NAME
Gupta	I-PERSON_NAME
Keysight	B-COMPANY
EEsof	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kendujhar	B-LOCATION
Bharat	B-CLIENT
Forge	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Systems	I-ROLE
Administrator	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Office	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
CDR	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
National	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Pharmaceutical	I-INSTITUTION
Education	I-INSTITUTION
and	I-INSTITUTION
Research	I-INSTITUTION
Mohali	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.3%	B-GRADE
Milind	B-PERSON_NAME
Mehta	I-PERSON_NAME
UpGrad	B-COMPANY
d,	O
Solan	B-LOCATION
n	O
Flowserve	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
UX	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
September	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
BHM	B-DEGREE
(Hons)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Additive	B-FIELD
Manufacturing	I-FIELD
,	O
ICFAI	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.8/10	B-GRADE
Heva	B-PERSON_NAME
Bisht	I-PERSON_NAME
Ribbon	B-COMPANY
Communications	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Khatima	B-LOCATION
CAMS	B-CLIENT
Head	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
Mobile	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Library	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Hardware	B-FIELD
in	I-FIELD
the	I-FIELD
Loop	I-FIELD
,	O
VNR	B-INSTITUTION
VJIET	I-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.2/10	B-GRADE
Zainab	B-PERSON_NAME
Shukla	I-PERSON_NAME
BEML	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kathua	B-LOCATION
Medanta	B-CLIENT
Data	B-ROLE
Governance	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2023	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Data	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Obstacle	B-FIELD
Detection	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Sri	I-INSTITUTION
City	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
77.5%	B-GRADE
Suresh	B-PERSON_NAME
Srinivasan	I-PERSON_NAME
Revolt	B-COMPANY
Intellicorp	I-COMPANY
,	O
Scheme	B-LOCATION
78	I-LOCATION
Indore	I-LOCATION
Qatar	B-CLIENT
National	I-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
API	B-ROLE
Documentation	I-ROLE
Specialist	I-ROLE
January	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
BBA	B-DEGREE
(Aviation)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Environmental	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
West	B-INSTITUTION
Bengal	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
68.5%	B-GRADE
Sarat	B-PERSON_NAME
George	I-PERSON_NAME
ZEE5	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ziro	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
CommScope	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
a	O
Senior	B-ROLE
DevOps	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
r	O
Sep	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Linguistics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Redundant	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.1/10	B-GRADE
Dayaram	B-PERSON_NAME
Singh	I-PERSON_NAME
Moonfrog	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
,	O
Cooch	B-LOCATION
Behar	I-LOCATION
Nidec	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Freelance	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Solar	I-DEGREE
Energy)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Packaging	B-FIELD
Innovation	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Gayatri	B-INSTITUTION
Vidya	I-INSTITUTION
Parishad	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
90.8%	B-GRADE
Divya	B-PERSON_NAME
Krishnan	I-PERSON_NAME
Niramai	B-COMPANY
,	O
Sivaganga	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Poorvika	B-CLIENT
Mobiles	I-CLIENT
SAP	B-ROLE
WM	I-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Voc	B-DEGREE
(Travel	I-DEGREE
&	I-DEGREE
Tourism)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Search	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NALSAR	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
72.9%	B-GRADE
Jyotsna	B-PERSON_NAME
Sundaram	I-PERSON_NAME
Groww	B-COMPANY
,	O
Nagarkurnool	B-LOCATION
Wipro	B-CLIENT
GE	I-CLIENT
Mobile	B-ROLE
Test	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
November	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Telugu)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Human	B-FIELD
Resource	I-FIELD
Information	I-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
BMS	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
90.6%	B-GRADE
Debasis	B-PERSON_NAME
Mukherjee	I-PERSON_NAME
Hinduja	B-COMPANY
Global	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
,	O
Chitradurga	B-LOCATION
Lucas	B-CLIENT
TVS	I-CLIENT
Blockchain	B-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
January	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Banking)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Mixed	B-FIELD
Reality	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Bangalore	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.1/10	B-GRADE
Shivraj	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Lendingkart	B-COMPANY
,	O
Mangalore	B-LOCATION
BHP	B-CLIENT
Build	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.E.	B-DEGREE
(IT)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Vehicular	B-FIELD
Networks	I-FIELD
,	O
Mohanlal	B-INSTITUTION
Sukhadia	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.3/10	B-GRADE
Anshuman	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyer	I-PERSON_NAME
3i	B-COMPANY
Infotech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Hebbal	B-LOCATION
Mysore	I-LOCATION
Columbia	B-CLIENT
Asia	I-CLIENT
Tier	B-ROLE
1	I-ROLE
SOC	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
MBA	B-DEGREE
(Digital	I-DEGREE
Marketing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Document	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
Raghu	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
57.1%	B-GRADE
Asha	B-PERSON_NAME
Chandrasekhar	I-PERSON_NAME
DTDC	B-COMPANY
Courier	I-COMPANY
,	O
East	B-LOCATION
Champaran	I-LOCATION
Orchid	B-CLIENT
Pharma	I-CLIENT
Salesforce	B-ROLE
CRM	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Apr	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PMP	B-DEGREE
–	O
Rapid	B-FIELD
Prototyping	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Waterloo	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.0/10	B-GRADE
Milan	B-PERSON_NAME
Trivedi	I-PERSON_NAME
Toshiba	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Bhind	B-LOCATION
Banorte	B-CLIENT
Oracle	B-ROLE
HCM	I-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Retail	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Graph	B-FIELD
Theory	I-FIELD
,	O
Deenbandhu	B-INSTITUTION
Chhotu	I-INSTITUTION
Ram	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.7/10	B-GRADE
Shreyas	B-PERSON_NAME
Rajagopalan	I-PERSON_NAME
Ola	B-COMPANY
Cabs	I-COMPANY
,	O
Davangere	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Heidelberg	B-CLIENT
Cement	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
DevOps	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
t	O
Feb	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
LL.B.	I-DEGREE
(Hons)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Graph	B-FIELD
Theory	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Goa	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.4/10	B-GRADE
Saroja	B-PERSON_NAME
Mehta	I-PERSON_NAME
Dozee	B-COMPANY
,	O
Mirik	B-LOCATION
SpiceJet	B-CLIENT
t	O
Informatica	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
June	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Distance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Fog	B-FIELD
Computing	I-FIELD
,	O
SSN	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.5/10	B-GRADE
Dharminder	B-PERSON_NAME
Chandrasekhar	I-PERSON_NAME
Nightingales	B-COMPANY
Home	I-COMPANY
Health	I-COMPANY
,	O
Gorakhpur	B-LOCATION
Prabhat	B-CLIENT
Dairy	I-CLIENT
Program	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
PMP	B-DEGREE
–	O
Genomics	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Qatar	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
85.6%	B-GRADE
Mrinalini	B-PERSON_NAME
Pillai	I-PERSON_NAME
Secureworks	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Mandla	B-LOCATION
Copa	B-CLIENT
Airlines	I-CLIENT
L3	B-ROLE
Support	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2021	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Interior	I-DEGREE
Design)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Dialogue	B-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Symbiosis	B-INSTITUTION
International	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
55.8%	B-GRADE
Shraddha	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyer	I-PERSON_NAME
NeoGrowth	B-COMPANY
Credit	I-COMPANY
t,	O
Alirajpur	B-LOCATION
r	O
Nestle	B-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Embedded	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Des.	B-DEGREE
(Interior)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Lifelong	B-FIELD
Learning	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IGDTUW	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
94.7%	B-GRADE
Swarupa	B-PERSON_NAME
Kaur	I-PERSON_NAME
Zomato	B-COMPANY
,	O
Sahebganj	B-LOCATION
Mitsubishi	B-CLIENT
Electric	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
QA	B-ROLE
Intern	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
B.Com	B-DEGREE
(E-Commerce)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Software	B-FIELD
Evolution	I-FIELD
,	O
Kurukshetra	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
74.3%	B-GRADE
Dayalu	B-PERSON_NAME
Agarwal	I-PERSON_NAME
AppInvent	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Mandla	B-LOCATION
a	O
Motorola	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Mobile	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Zoology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Body	B-FIELD
Area	I-FIELD
Networks	I-FIELD
,	O
MSIT	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.9/10	B-GRADE
Shobhana	B-PERSON_NAME
Gupta	I-PERSON_NAME
Kingston	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Banda	B-LOCATION
Vedanta	B-CLIENT
Aluminium	I-CLIENT
Rust	B-ROLE
Blockchain	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Education)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Naive	B-FIELD
Bayes	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Arunachal	I-INSTITUTION
Pradesh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
77.5%	B-GRADE
Guddi	B-PERSON_NAME
Sen	I-PERSON_NAME
Moog	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kottayam	B-LOCATION
Freecharge	B-CLIENT
PCB	B-ROLE
Design	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Yoga	I-DEGREE
&	I-DEGREE
Naturopathy)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Digital	B-FIELD
Asset	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
IIM	B-INSTITUTION
Indore	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.4%	B-GRADE
Akshitha	B-PERSON_NAME
Raheem	I-PERSON_NAME
Bijak	B-COMPANY
Agritech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Seraikela	B-LOCATION
Kharsawan	I-LOCATION
Flying	B-CLIENT
Machine	I-CLIENT
Risk	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
PGDM	B-DEGREE
(Marketing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Digital	B-FIELD
Manufacturing	I-FIELD
,	O
Dayananda	B-INSTITUTION
Sagar	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.8/10	B-GRADE
Ramesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Banerjee	I-PERSON_NAME
Kuku	B-COMPANY
FM	I-COMPANY
,	O
Daman	B-LOCATION
Pilgrim	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Prototyping	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
October	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
M.E.	B-DEGREE
(Env)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Customer	B-FIELD
Relationship	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Central	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Haryana	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.9/10	B-GRADE
Gajendra	B-PERSON_NAME
Desai	I-PERSON_NAME
Teleperformance	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Dehradun	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Imagine	B-CLIENT
Apple	I-CLIENT
Reseller	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
DevOps	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
r	O
August	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Arch.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Curriculum	B-FIELD
Learning	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
UIET	B-INSTITUTION
Chandigarh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
88.1%	B-GRADE
Ashwini	B-PERSON_NAME
Nair	I-PERSON_NAME
Folio3	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Guindy	B-LOCATION
Chennai	I-LOCATION
Sun	B-CLIENT
Direct	I-CLIENT
Algorithmic	B-ROLE
Trading	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
LL.M.	B-DEGREE
(Cyber	I-DEGREE
Law)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Hyperparameter	B-FIELD
Optimization	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
National	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Design	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
69.1%	B-GRADE
Abhishek	B-PERSON_NAME
Tiwari	I-PERSON_NAME
Keysight	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ghazipur	B-LOCATION
Vodafone	B-CLIENT
UK	I-CLIENT
Data	B-ROLE
Protection	I-ROLE
Officer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Advertising)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Data	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
Professor	B-INSTITUTION
Jayashankar	I-INSTITUTION
Telangana	I-INSTITUTION
State	I-INSTITUTION
Agricultural	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
86.2%	B-GRADE
Ketan	B-PERSON_NAME
Dubey	I-PERSON_NAME
Workday	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Golf	B-LOCATION
Course	I-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Gurugram	I-LOCATION
IOC	B-CLIENT
EV	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
GCP	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Mar	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Agri)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Tissue	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Kancheepuram	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.1/10	B-GRADE
Zoya	B-PERSON_NAME
Sheikh	I-PERSON_NAME
Thermo	B-COMPANY
Fisher	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Siripuram	B-LOCATION
Visakhapatnam	I-LOCATION
Ambev	B-CLIENT
Salesforce	B-ROLE
Administrator	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(CE)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Product	B-FIELD
Lifecycle	I-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
IIM	B-INSTITUTION
Sambalpur	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.3/10	B-GRADE
Vrinda	B-PERSON_NAME
Ramachandran	I-PERSON_NAME
Radixweb	B-COMPANY
,	O
Warangal	B-LOCATION
GE	B-CLIENT
Grid	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
NOC	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Zoology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Technology	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
KU	B-INSTITUTION
Leuven	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
78.3%	B-GRADE
Chitralekha	B-PERSON_NAME
Rani	I-PERSON_NAME
Elsner	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kalasatama	B-LOCATION
Smart	I-LOCATION
City	I-LOCATION
Rayzon	B-CLIENT
Solar	I-CLIENT
Node.js	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Sep	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Computational	B-FIELD
Chemistry	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Tiruchirappalli	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
91.1%	B-GRADE
Nupura	B-PERSON_NAME
Ghosh	I-PERSON_NAME
Intelegain	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Peenya	B-LOCATION
Bangalore	I-LOCATION
SEW	B-CLIENT
Eurodrive	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Reliability	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
July	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(VR/AR)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Fire	B-FIELD
Detection	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NLU	B-INSTITUTION
Odisha	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.4/10	B-GRADE
Tapasi	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhatt	I-PERSON_NAME
Wind	B-COMPANY
River	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Lakshadweep	B-LOCATION
Diageo	B-CLIENT
Automation	B-ROLE
Anywhere	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
+	I-DEGREE
B.Ed.	I-DEGREE
(Integrated)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Web	B-FIELD
Mining	I-FIELD
,	O
Plaksha	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
61.4%	B-GRADE
Sukalyan	B-PERSON_NAME
Deshpande	I-PERSON_NAME
Sony	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
R&D	I-COMPANY
,	O
IndiaBulls	B-LOCATION
Finance	I-LOCATION
Centre	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
i	O
Vestige	B-CLIENT
Marketing	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
QA	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
Online	B-DEGREE
MBA	I-DEGREE
–	O
Data	B-FIELD
Lakehouse	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
North	B-INSTITUTION
Eastern	I-INSTITUTION
Hill	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
78.8%	B-GRADE
Ashima	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
Adda52	B-COMPANY
,	O
Koramangala	B-LOCATION
Bangalore	I-LOCATION
Lifestyle	B-CLIENT
International	I-CLIENT
Data	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
FRM	B-DEGREE
–	O
Text	B-FIELD
Mining	I-FIELD
,	O
DTU	B-INSTITUTION
Delhi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
64.5%	B-GRADE
Amitabh	B-PERSON_NAME
Sandhu	I-PERSON_NAME
Coforge	B-COMPANY
,	O
Saravanampatti	B-LOCATION
Coimbatore	I-LOCATION
Spencers	B-CLIENT
Retail	I-CLIENT
Big	B-ROLE
Data	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Tourism	I-DEGREE
Mgmt)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Road	B-FIELD
Surface	I-FIELD
Analysis	I-FIELD
,	O
Ranchi	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.4/10	B-GRADE
Moumita	B-PERSON_NAME
Roy	I-PERSON_NAME
QBurst	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Vidisha	B-LOCATION
Avenue	B-CLIENT
Supermarts	I-CLIENT
VDI	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
ISO	B-DEGREE
Lead	I-DEGREE
Auditor	I-DEGREE
–	O
Network	B-FIELD
Function	I-FIELD
Virtualization	I-FIELD
,	O
Calcutta	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
88.6%	B-GRADE
Hira	B-PERSON_NAME
Singh	I-PERSON_NAME
ITC	B-COMPANY
Infotech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Lalitpur	B-LOCATION
UniCredit	B-CLIENT
t	O
Senior	B-ROLE
IoT	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
January	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2016	I-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Water	I-DEGREE
Resources)	I-DEGREE
–	O
ML	B-FIELD
Ops	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Heritage	B-INSTITUTION
Institute	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Technology	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.7/10	B-GRADE
Priyam	B-PERSON_NAME
Kumar	I-PERSON_NAME
Leadsquared	B-COMPANY
,	O
Patia	B-LOCATION
Bhubaneswar	I-LOCATION
Akzo	B-CLIENT
Nobel	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Container	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
April	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
PGDBA	B-DEGREE
–	O
Caching	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Anant	B-INSTITUTION
National	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
87.0%	B-GRADE
Ganesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Deshpande	I-PERSON_NAME
Successive	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kawardha	B-LOCATION
Telefonica	B-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Business	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Sep	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
October	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
ISO	B-DEGREE
Lead	I-DEGREE
Auditor	I-DEGREE
–	O
Road	B-FIELD
Surface	I-FIELD
Analysis	I-FIELD
,	O
Professor	B-INSTITUTION
Jayashankar	I-INSTITUTION
Telangana	I-INSTITUTION
State	I-INSTITUTION
Agricultural	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.1/10	B-GRADE
Avni	B-PERSON_NAME
Srivastava	I-PERSON_NAME
Remidio	B-COMPANY
Innovative	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
,	O
Purnia	B-LOCATION
SMC	B-CLIENT
Global	I-CLIENT
Digital	B-ROLE
Forensics	I-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
March	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Nursing)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Semantic	B-FIELD
Search	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Nanyang	B-INSTITUTION
Technological	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.1/10	B-GRADE
Alpesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Tiwari	I-PERSON_NAME
Microland	B-COMPANY
,	O
Lakhisarai	B-LOCATION
ICICI	B-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
iOS	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
Apr	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Geophysics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
RF	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
Govind	B-INSTITUTION
Guru	I-INSTITUTION
Tribal	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.7/10	B-GRADE
Nimisha	B-PERSON_NAME
Desai	I-PERSON_NAME
Agilent	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Paschim	B-LOCATION
Bardhaman	I-LOCATION
Heidelberg	B-CLIENT
Cement	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
PeopleSoft	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
Nov	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
February	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Cyber	I-DEGREE
Security)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Declarative	B-FIELD
Programming	I-FIELD
,	O
Assam	B-INSTITUTION
Don	I-INSTITUTION
Bosco	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.0/10	B-GRADE
Sankalp	B-PERSON_NAME
Sandhu	I-PERSON_NAME
Nvidia	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Jodhpur	B-LOCATION
Kerala	B-CLIENT
Vision	I-CLIENT
Pipeline	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
Aug	B-DATE_END
2017	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(UAV)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Brain	B-FIELD
Computer	I-FIELD
Interface	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Wisconsin	I-INSTITUTION
Madison	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.7/10	B-GRADE
Ashok	B-PERSON_NAME
Murugan	I-PERSON_NAME
OYO	B-COMPANY
Rooms	I-COMPANY
,	O
Bidar	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Dot	B-CLIENT
&	I-CLIENT
Key	I-CLIENT
ABAP	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
January	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Social	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Open	B-FIELD
Banking	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Easwari	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
92.3%	B-GRADE
Ramanujam	B-PERSON_NAME
Srinivasan	I-PERSON_NAME
Eaton	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Auraiya	B-LOCATION
Amadeus	B-CLIENT
IT	I-CLIENT
Purple	B-ROLE
Team	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
September	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Ophthalmic)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Peer	B-FIELD
Review	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Sambalpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
94.6%	B-GRADE
Mudra	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhat	I-PERSON_NAME
SumTotal	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
a,	O
Amanora	B-LOCATION
Park	I-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
e	O
Vedanta	B-CLIENT
Aluminium	I-CLIENT
Solutions	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Apr	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Nano	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Extreme	B-FIELD
Programming	I-FIELD
,	O
Techno	B-INSTITUTION
India	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.4/10	B-GRADE
Mayuri	B-PERSON_NAME
Patel	I-PERSON_NAME
Myntra	B-COMPANY
,	O
Navi	B-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Koparkhairane	I-LOCATION
Raymond	B-CLIENT
Retail	I-CLIENT
Product	B-ROLE
Owner	I-ROLE
Apr	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
(Tourism)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Remote	B-FIELD
Work	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Edinburgh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.4/10	B-GRADE
Poonam	B-PERSON_NAME
Thomas	I-PERSON_NAME
CaratLane	B-COMPANY
e,	O
Majuli	B-LOCATION
i	O
Yatra	B-CLIENT
Online	I-CLIENT
Staff	B-ROLE
Network	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Sericulture)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Optical	B-FIELD
Communication	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Warwick	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.1/10	B-GRADE
Shriram	B-PERSON_NAME
Shah	I-PERSON_NAME
Mobisoft	B-COMPANY
Infotech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Wakad	B-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
Gap	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Monitoring	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
MCA	B-DEGREE
(Cyber	I-DEGREE
Security)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Aerial	B-FIELD
Robotics	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Nagpur	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.1/10	B-GRADE
Sukhvinder	B-PERSON_NAME
Patil	I-PERSON_NAME
Sun	B-COMPANY
NXT	I-COMPANY
,	O
Mysore	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Bangalore	I-LOCATION
Metro	B-CLIENT
Cash	I-CLIENT
and	I-CLIENT
Carry	I-CLIENT
DSP	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Investment	I-DEGREE
Banking)	I-DEGREE
–	O
System	B-FIELD
on	I-FIELD
Chip	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Mandi	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.3/10	B-GRADE
Bhavna	B-PERSON_NAME
Roy	I-PERSON_NAME
OkCredit	B-COMPANY
t,	O
Mumbai	B-LOCATION
i	O
Vivo	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Unity	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Machine	I-DEGREE
Learning)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Chemical	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
Central	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Punjab	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
65.1%	B-GRADE
Ananthaswamy	B-PERSON_NAME
Subramanian	I-PERSON_NAME
Jai	B-COMPANY
Kisan	I-COMPANY
,	O
Purnia	B-LOCATION
Lupin	B-CLIENT
Game	B-ROLE
QA	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
(Anthropology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Computer	B-FIELD
Organization	I-FIELD
,	O
Stanford	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
60.6%	B-GRADE
Balakrishna	B-PERSON_NAME
Mishra	I-PERSON_NAME
Nihilent	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Krishnagiri	B-LOCATION
Grupo	B-CLIENT
Bimbo	I-CLIENT
Help	B-ROLE
Desk	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
September	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Mass	I-DEGREE
Communication)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Predictive	B-FIELD
Maintenance	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Manipur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
71.3%	B-GRADE
Babita	B-PERSON_NAME
Chauhan	I-PERSON_NAME
Avaya	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Mysore	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Bangalore	I-LOCATION
Siemens	B-CLIENT
Energy	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Hibernate	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2010	I-DATE_START
–	O
August	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
B.Pharm	B-DEGREE
–	O
Information	B-FIELD
Architecture	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Surat	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
56.5%	B-GRADE
Subhadeep	B-PERSON_NAME
Pandey	I-PERSON_NAME
Druva	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Thrissur	B-LOCATION
Rural	I-LOCATION
Bodal	B-CLIENT
Chemicals	I-CLIENT
ML	B-ROLE
Platform	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Nov	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Health	I-DEGREE
Informatics)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Civil	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
Presidency	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
Chennai	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.4/10	B-GRADE
Ayush	B-PERSON_NAME
Balasubramanian	I-PERSON_NAME
Toshiba	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Chittoor	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Coal	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Web	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
BPT	B-DEGREE
–	O
NewSQL	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
y,	O
ICFAI	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
y,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
6,	O
77.0%	B-GRADE
%	O
Sudhir	B-PERSON_NAME
Balasubramanian	I-PERSON_NAME
WebClues	B-COMPANY
Infotech	I-COMPANY
h,	O
Integrated	B-LOCATION
Industrial	I-LOCATION
Township	I-LOCATION
Tumkur	I-LOCATION
r	O
Bridgestone	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Redis	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
May	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2021	I-DATE_END
BDS	B-DEGREE
–	O
Brain	B-FIELD
Computer	I-FIELD
Interface	I-FIELD
,	O
Nanyang	B-INSTITUTION
Technological	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.4/10	B-GRADE
Debyendu	B-PERSON_NAME
Menon	I-PERSON_NAME
Bharat	B-COMPANY
Forge	I-COMPANY
Digital	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kondapur	B-LOCATION
Hyderabad	I-LOCATION
Tata	B-CLIENT
Solar	I-CLIENT
ASIC	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
January	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
MOT	B-DEGREE
–	O
Microwave	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Tiruchirappalli	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
71.9%	B-GRADE
Sai	B-PERSON_NAME
Mishra	I-PERSON_NAME
Zoho	B-COMPANY
Corporation	I-COMPANY
,	O
Blue	B-LOCATION
Ridge	I-LOCATION
Pune	I-LOCATION
Bunge	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
UI	B-ROLE
Designer	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Sports	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Fault	B-FIELD
Tolerant	I-FIELD
Computing	I-FIELD
,	O
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Kakinada	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.5/10	B-GRADE
Amol	B-PERSON_NAME
Reddy	I-PERSON_NAME
Cognizant	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Dwarka	B-LOCATION
Delhi	I-LOCATION
Sun	B-CLIENT
TV	I-CLIENT
Director	B-ROLE
of	I-ROLE
QA	I-ROLE
July	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(IT)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Video	B-FIELD
Conferencing	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Caltech	B-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
85.6%	B-GRADE
Bhumika	B-PERSON_NAME
Dey	I-PERSON_NAME
Josh	B-COMPANY
by	I-COMPANY
Dailyhunt	I-COMPANY
,	O
Airoli	B-LOCATION
Navi	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Indoco	B-CLIENT
Remedies	I-CLIENT
Growth	B-ROLE
Product	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Oct	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
October	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Poultry	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Data	B-FIELD
Lake	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Anant	B-INSTITUTION
National	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.6/10	B-GRADE
Siddhesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Bhat	I-PERSON_NAME
Hoichoi	B-COMPANY
,	O
Suryapet	B-LOCATION
Telangana	I-LOCATION
Commonwealth	B-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
Data	B-ROLE
Integration	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jul	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Game	I-DEGREE
Design)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Energy	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
,	O
Mizoram	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2016	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
72.8%	B-GRADE
Preethi	B-PERSON_NAME
Menon	I-PERSON_NAME
Grafana	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Suryapet	B-LOCATION
Avianca	B-CLIENT
IT	B-ROLE
Consultant	I-ROLE
November	B-DATE_START
2018	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.A.	B-DEGREE
(Event	I-DEGREE
Management)	I-DEGREE
–	O
System	B-FIELD
Integration	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Nagaland	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2020	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
56.3%	B-GRADE
Hardik	B-PERSON_NAME
Patil	I-PERSON_NAME
Cohesity	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Bogadi	B-LOCATION
Mysore	I-LOCATION
Copa	B-CLIENT
Airlines	I-CLIENT
Robotics	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Feb	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Microbiology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Scene	B-FIELD
Understanding	I-FIELD
,	O
Cummins	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
Pune	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
86.0%	B-GRADE
Naveen	B-PERSON_NAME
Kumar	I-PERSON_NAME
Semtech	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sircilla	B-LOCATION
Access	B-CLIENT
Bank	I-CLIENT
RPA	B-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
September	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(OT)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Multimedia	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Madras	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.0/10	B-GRADE
Sonalee	B-PERSON_NAME
Rajagopalan	I-PERSON_NAME
Daffodil	B-COMPANY
Software	I-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Ghodbunder	B-LOCATION
Road	I-LOCATION
Thane	I-LOCATION
SPX	B-CLIENT
Flow	I-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
iOS	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
Oct	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2014	I-DATE_END
B.Des.	B-DEGREE
(Animation)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Legal	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Indian	B-INSTITUTION
Maritime	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
87.2%	B-GRADE
Muthukumar	B-PERSON_NAME
Raghavan	I-PERSON_NAME
Ubiquiti	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
DLF	B-LOCATION
Cyber	I-LOCATION
Park	I-LOCATION
Gurugram	I-LOCATION
Imagine	B-CLIENT
Apple	I-CLIENT
Reseller	I-CLIENT
JavaScript	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
July	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2015	I-DATE_END
M.Lib.I.Sc.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Thermal	B-FIELD
Analysis	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
EPFL	B-INSTITUTION
Switzerland	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
89.3%	B-GRADE
Pranav	B-PERSON_NAME
Wagh	I-PERSON_NAME
AlmaBetter	B-COMPANY
r,	O
Madurai	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Aptiv	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Feb	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
B.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Ceramic)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Surgical	B-FIELD
Robotics	I-FIELD
,	O
Kolhan	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2013	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
80.7%	B-GRADE
Surendra	B-PERSON_NAME
Begum	I-PERSON_NAME
SunTec	B-COMPANY
Business	I-COMPANY
Solutions	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Platina	B-LOCATION
BKC	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
i	O
Oriflame	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Distinguished	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2019	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Horticulture)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Digital	B-FIELD
Factory	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hyderabad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
79.2%	B-GRADE
Jayesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Malik	I-PERSON_NAME
Mohalla	B-COMPANY
Tech	I-COMPANY
,	O
Sidhi	B-LOCATION
GRSE	B-CLIENT
Network	B-ROLE
Operations	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
August	B-DATE_START
2015	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jan	B-DATE_END
2022	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Culinary	I-DEGREE
Arts)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Business	B-FIELD
Continuity	I-FIELD
,	O
AIIMS	B-INSTITUTION
Bhubaneswar	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.6/10	B-GRADE
Anshul	B-PERSON_NAME
Shankar	I-PERSON_NAME
Eka	B-COMPANY
Care	I-COMPANY
,	O
Buxar	B-LOCATION
Sun	B-CLIENT
TV	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Program	I-ROLE
Manager	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
B.Com	B-DEGREE
LL.B.	I-DEGREE
–	O
Soft	B-FIELD
Robotics	I-FIELD
,	O
MIT	B-INSTITUTION
World	I-INSTITUTION
Peace	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.0/10	B-GRADE
Ayesha	B-PERSON_NAME
Tripathi	I-PERSON_NAME
PharmEasy	B-COMPANY
y,	O
Platina	B-LOCATION
BKC	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
i	O
Sea	B-CLIENT
Limited	I-CLIENT
Lead	B-ROLE
Performance	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
June	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Insurance)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Industrial	B-FIELD
Engineering	I-FIELD
,	O
TAPMI	B-INSTITUTION
Manipal	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2010	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.0/10	B-GRADE
Avijit	B-PERSON_NAME
Yadav	I-PERSON_NAME
Gradeup	B-COMPANY
(BYJU's	I-COMPANY
Exam	I-COMPANY
Prep)	I-COMPANY
,	O
Jabalpur	B-LOCATION
Nirmal	B-CLIENT
Bang	I-CLIENT
IoT	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
t	O
Sep	B-DATE_START
2012	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Tech	B-DEGREE
(Instrumentation)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Social	B-FIELD
Media	I-FIELD
Analytics	I-FIELD
,	O
Central	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Ladakh	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2019	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
93.8%	B-GRADE
Avantika	B-PERSON_NAME
Tiwari	I-PERSON_NAME
Satyukt	B-COMPANY
Analytics	I-COMPANY
,	O
Nainital	B-LOCATION
Oppo	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
IT	B-ROLE
Auditor	I-ROLE
February	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
B.Des.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Microservices	B-FIELD
,	O
Ajeenkya	B-INSTITUTION
DY	I-INSTITUTION
Patil	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2014	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.1/10	B-GRADE
Sanjna	B-PERSON_NAME
Bains	I-PERSON_NAME
Marg	B-COMPANY
ERP	I-COMPANY
,	O
Rohtas	B-LOCATION
NN	B-CLIENT
Group	I-CLIENT
Camunda	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Dec	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Oct	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
Ph.D	B-DEGREE
(Agriculture)	I-DEGREE
–	O
AI	B-FIELD
Ops	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
JNTU	B-INSTITUTION
Kakinada	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
78.2%	B-GRADE
Sushant	B-PERSON_NAME
Siddiqui	I-PERSON_NAME
Hoichoi	B-COMPANY
,	O
Una	B-LOCATION
Vedant	B-CLIENT
Fashions	I-CLIENT
Microsoft	B-ROLE
Dynamics	I-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
LL.B.	B-DEGREE
(Online)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Fleet	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Kurukshetra	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2021	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
7.8/10	B-GRADE
Shivam	B-PERSON_NAME
Murugan	I-PERSON_NAME
Stanza	B-COMPANY
Living	I-COMPANY
,	O
Pauri	B-LOCATION
Nike	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
API	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
September	B-DATE_START
2020	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2012	I-DATE_END
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Environmental	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Citizen	B-FIELD
Development	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Melbourne	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
82.6%	B-GRADE
Rajshree	B-PERSON_NAME
Natarajan	I-PERSON_NAME
Inshorts	B-COMPANY
,	O
Mindspace	B-LOCATION
Airoli	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
ZF	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Principal	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2013	I-DATE_END
CFA	B-DEGREE
(Chartered	I-DEGREE
Financial	I-DEGREE
Analyst)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Facility	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
Systems	I-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Hamirpur	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
73.7%	B-GRADE
Mala	B-PERSON_NAME
Mathew	I-PERSON_NAME
Hexaware	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Siliguri	B-LOCATION
Manappuram	B-CLIENT
Finance	I-CLIENT
Dimensional	B-ROLE
Modeler	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2022	I-DATE_START
–	O
Feb	B-DATE_END
2020	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(CS)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Graph	B-FIELD
Theory	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
New	I-INSTITUTION
South	I-INSTITUTION
Wales	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2011	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
6.3/10	B-GRADE
Sonali	B-PERSON_NAME
Iyengar	I-PERSON_NAME
JioSaavn	B-COMPANY
n,	O
Madurai	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Azure	B-CLIENT
Power	I-CLIENT
HTML/CSS	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
April	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
May	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
B.A.	B-DEGREE
LL.B.	I-DEGREE
(Hons)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Citizen	B-FIELD
Science	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIIT	B-INSTITUTION
Allahabad	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
69.2%	B-GRADE
Ramalinga	B-PERSON_NAME
Venkataraman	I-PERSON_NAME
DealShare	B-COMPANY
e,	O
Koppal	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
b	O
Bajaj	B-CLIENT
Electronics	I-CLIENT
Software	B-ROLE
Architect	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2014	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jun	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
MBA	B-DEGREE
(Healthcare)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Workforce	B-FIELD
Management	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Sambalpur	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2018	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
65.1%	B-GRADE
Sumati	B-PERSON_NAME
Banerjee	I-PERSON_NAME
InstaSafe	B-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
s,	O
Karimganj	B-LOCATION
j	O
Ujjivan	B-CLIENT
Small	I-CLIENT
Finance	I-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Gameplay	I-ROLE
Programmer	I-ROLE
Jan	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
December	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
Diploma	B-DEGREE
(Secretarial	I-DEGREE
Practice)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Ethical	B-FIELD
Hacking	I-FIELD
,	O
Cummins	B-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
Pune	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2017	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
83.0%	B-GRADE
Safdar	B-PERSON_NAME
Dey	I-PERSON_NAME
Exotel	B-COMPANY
,	O
Jhargram	B-LOCATION
Havells	B-CLIENT
Cables	I-CLIENT
TestNG	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
r	O
November	B-DATE_START
2011	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2018	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Electric	I-DEGREE
Vehicle	I-DEGREE
Technology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Reporting	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Nanyang	B-INSTITUTION
Technological	I-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
80.7%	B-GRADE
Gopal	B-PERSON_NAME
Pawar	I-PERSON_NAME
Inshorts	B-COMPANY
,	O
Navi	B-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
RCF	B-CLIENT
India	I-CLIENT
Cloud	B-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
December	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Plant	I-DEGREE
Pathology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Environmental	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Easwari	B-INSTITUTION
Engineering	I-INSTITUTION
College	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2022	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
60.3%	B-GRADE
Reva	B-PERSON_NAME
Kumar	I-PERSON_NAME
Nagarro	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Malda	B-LOCATION
Cyient	B-CLIENT
Lua	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
August	B-DATE_START
2023	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Soil	I-DEGREE
Science)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Biotechnology	B-FIELD
,	O
NIT	B-INSTITUTION
Nagaland	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2023	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
78.2%	B-GRADE
Bhavesh	B-PERSON_NAME
Gupta	I-PERSON_NAME
Hughes	B-COMPANY
India	I-COMPANY
,	O
Nehru	B-LOCATION
Place	I-LOCATION
Delhi	I-LOCATION
KPIT	B-CLIENT
Technologies	I-CLIENT
C++	B-ROLE
Developer	I-ROLE
Mar	B-DATE_START
2016	I-DATE_START
–	O
Present	B-DATE_END
Six	B-DEGREE
Sigma	I-DEGREE
Green	I-DEGREE
Belt	I-DEGREE
–	O
Edge	B-FIELD
Computing	I-FIELD
,	O
Central	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
of	I-INSTITUTION
Bihar	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2015	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
80.1%	B-GRADE
Farhan	B-PERSON_NAME
Patil	I-PERSON_NAME
DocPrime	B-COMPANY
e,	O
Lonavala	B-LOCATION
a	O
HPCL	B-CLIENT
Senior	B-ROLE
Software	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Aug	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
Jul	B-DATE_END
2019	I-DATE_END
PG	B-DEGREE
Diploma	I-DEGREE
(Banking)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Emission	B-FIELD
Monitoring	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
IIT	B-INSTITUTION
Kharagpur	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
9.4/10	B-GRADE
Nilima	B-PERSON_NAME
Shukla	I-PERSON_NAME
Open	B-COMPANY
Financial	I-COMPANY
Technologies	I-COMPANY
,	O
Kadapa	B-LOCATION
IT	I-LOCATION
Hub	I-LOCATION
Big	B-CLIENT
Bazaar	I-CLIENT
BI	B-ROLE
Analyst	I-ROLE
Nov	B-DATE_START
2013	I-DATE_START
–	O
Sep	B-DATE_END
2011	I-DATE_END
M.Ed.	B-DEGREE
–	O
Intrusion	B-FIELD
Prevention	I-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
Osmania	B-INSTITUTION
University	I-INSTITUTION
,	O
2012	B-EDU_YEAR_END
,	O
8.2/10	B-GRADE
Sidhant	B-PERSON_NAME
Das	I-PERSON_NAME
Inshorts	B-COMPANY
,	O
Andheri	B-LOCATION
West	I-LOCATION
Mumbai	I-LOCATION
Jio	B-CLIENT
Phone	I-CLIENT
Web	B-ROLE
Performance	I-ROLE
Engineer	I-ROLE
Jun	B-DATE_START
2017	I-DATE_START
–	O
March	B-DATE_END
2010	I-DATE_END
M.Sc	B-DEGREE
(Microbiology)	I-DEGREE
–	O
Stacking	B-FIELD
Technology	I-FIELD
,	O
University	B-INSTITUTION
