[
  {
    "id": 4063,
    "tokens": [
      "Cloudera",
      "—",
      "Principal",
      "Engineer",
      "—",
      "Denver,",
      "CO",
      "—",
      "Client:",
      "Xcel",
      "Energy",
      "—",
      "Jan",
      "2022–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2236,
    "tokens": [
      "[\"M.Tech\",",
      "\"Distributed",
      "Systems\",",
      "\"NIT",
      "Warangal\",",
      "\"2010-2012\",",
      "\"89.6%\"]"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2163,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech,",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "and",
      "Engineering,",
      "Andhra",
      "University",
      "|",
      "2008-2012",
      "|",
      "72.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "tokens": [
      "Oracle,",
      "Santa",
      "Clara,",
      "CA",
      "-",
      "Java",
      "Developer",
      "(August",
      "2014–December",
      "2016)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2934,
    "tokens": [
      "Aug",
      "2018",
      "–",
      "Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3383,
    "tokens": [
      "(Stellar",
      "Stellar",
      "Pvt",
      "Ltd)",
      "(Security",
      "Engineer)",
      "(client:Infinite",
      "Hospitality",
      "S.p.A.)",
      "(Bangalore)",
      "(2017–2019)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1499,
    "tokens": [
      "Before",
      "that",
      "at",
      "BrowserStack",
      "as",
      "QA",
      "Engineer",
      "from",
      "Jan",
      "2020",
      "to",
      "Aug",
      "2022,",
      "Mumbai,",
      "client:",
      "Enterprise",
      "SaaS"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3060,
    "tokens": [
      "{TITLE}",
      "Senior",
      "Analyst"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1576,
    "tokens": [
      "Completed",
      "my",
      "B.Sc",
      "Biotechnology",
      "from",
      "Osmania",
      "University",
      "(2006-2009)",
      "with",
      "7.6",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3242,
    "tokens": [
      "2022.04",
      ">",
      "Now",
      "Lead",
      "Developer",
      "Meesho",
      "Inc.",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1993,
    "tokens": [
      "Feb",
      "2020",
      "–",
      "Till",
      "Date",
      "|",
      "ML",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Mu",
      "Sigma",
      "|",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3233,
    "tokens": [
      "Infinite",
      "Hospitality",
      "S.p.A.",
      "Junior",
      "Data",
      "Scientist",
      "Bangalore",
      "2016/09",
      "-",
      "2019/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4234,
    "tokens": [
      "Redshift",
      "AWS",
      "|",
      "Sr.",
      "Data",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Seattle,",
      "WA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Expedia",
      "|",
      "(Oct",
      "2018",
      "-",
      "Feb",
      "2021)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2807,
    "tokens": [
      "BEng",
      "Electrical",
      "Engineering",
      "-",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Illinois",
      "Chicago",
      "-",
      "Graduated",
      "2013",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.6"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4243,
    "tokens": [
      "Databricks",
      "|",
      "Staff",
      "Data",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Adobe",
      "|",
      "2022-Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1052,
    "tokens": [
      "Jadavpur",
      "University",
      ">>",
      "M.Tech",
      ">>",
      "2012-2014",
      ">>",
      "82.6%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2362,
    "tokens": [
      "Institute",
      ">>",
      "Osmania",
      "University"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1389,
    "tokens": [
      "___GE",
      "Healthcare___",
      "|",
      "___Consultant___",
      "|",
      "___Bangalore___",
      "|",
      "___2012–2016___"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1843,
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Biology",
      "-",
      "Purdue",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2007",
      "to",
      "2011",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1561,
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech,",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Mysore,",
      "2017-2019,",
      "87.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4376,
    "tokens": [
      "Cloudera",
      "|",
      "Data",
      "Engineer",
      "-",
      "Santa",
      "Clara",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Cisco",
      "-",
      "May",
      "2019-Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2856,
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Finance",
      "-",
      "UC",
      "Berkeley",
      "Haas",
      "School",
      "of",
      "Business",
      "-",
      "Graduated",
      "2018",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.9"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 367,
    "tokens": [
      "Graduated:",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 902,
    "tokens": [
      "PriorRole:LeadAnalyst,CapgeminiGurgaon,2017-2020client>IBM"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2589,
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Marketing",
      "Analytics",
      "-",
      "Boston",
      "University",
      "-",
      "Graduated",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1547,
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech,",
      "NIT",
      "Trichy,",
      "2012-2014,",
      "84.0%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1557,
    "tokens": [
      "Intern",
      "@",
      "TCS",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "May",
      "2017",
      "-",
      "Jul",
      "2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 607,
    "tokens": [
      "Jun",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "Dec",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1302,
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.:",
      "CSE",
      "@",
      "SSN",
      "College",
      "of",
      "Engineering",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "2014-2018",
      "|",
      "CGPA",
      "8.3"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4032,
    "tokens": [
      "Education",
      "2014-2016:",
      "M.S.",
      "Data",
      "Science,",
      "UC",
      "Berkeley,",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3097,
    "tokens": [
      "Soft",
      "Soft",
      "GmbH",
      "::",
      "Associate",
      "Product",
      "Manager",
      "(APM)",
      "::",
      "Chennai",
      "::",
      "Apr",
      "2018",
      "→",
      "Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2687,
    "tokens": [
      "iwoca",
      "-",
      "Head",
      "of",
      "Credit",
      "Risk",
      "-",
      "London,",
      "EC2M",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "British",
      "Business",
      "Bank",
      "-",
      "09/2017",
      "to",
      "04/2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1663,
    "tokens": [
      "2014–2017",
      "|",
      "Synchrony",
      "Medical",
      "|",
      "Medical",
      "Writer",
      "|",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 491,
    "tokens": [
      "Genpact",
      "India,",
      "Gurugram"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2727,
    "tokens": [
      "BCA",
      ">>",
      "JNTU",
      "Hyderabad",
      "[2015–18]",
      "(58%)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1227,
    "tokens": [
      "Tata",
      "Consultancy",
      "Services#Python",
      "Lead#Lucknow#2019-2022#Client:Nykaa"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2845,
    "tokens": [
      "Tractable",
      "-",
      "Director",
      "of",
      "AI",
      "Research",
      "-",
      "London,",
      "N1C",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "RSA",
      "Insurance",
      "Group",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "07/2021",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2615,
    "tokens": [
      "Bangalore,",
      "Karnataka",
      "|",
      "2021",
      "-",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1836,
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Business",
      "Analytics",
      "→",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Utah",
      "→",
      "2012–2014",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1101,
    "tokens": [
      "MCA|Nirma",
      "University|Ahmedabad|2008|2010|cgpa:7.3/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 865,
    "tokens": [
      "networkEngineer@cisco@Pune@2018@present@client:airtel"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2397,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "/",
      "EEE",
      "/",
      "NIT",
      "Trichy",
      "Tamil",
      "Nadu",
      "/",
      "2012–2016",
      "/",
      "CGPA",
      "8.0"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2038,
    "tokens": [
      "Zilch",
      "Technology",
      "→",
      "Growth",
      "Marketing",
      "Lead",
      "→",
      "London,",
      "SW1V",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "American",
      "Express",
      "UK",
      "→",
      "Feb",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech,",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "and",
      "Engineering,",
      "NIT",
      "Trichy,",
      "2018,",
      "CPI:",
      "8.72"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 331,
    "tokens": [
      "Trainee",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1884,
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Human",
      "Resource",
      "Management",
      "-",
      "DePaul",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2011",
      "to",
      "2013",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.6"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2100,
    "tokens": [
      "Full",
      "Stack",
      "Developer:",
      "Zomato",
      "|",
      "Location:",
      "Gurugram",
      "|",
      "Tenure:",
      "2022–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2800,
    "tokens": [
      "Bottomline",
      "Technologies",
      "→",
      "Graduate",
      "Developer",
      "→",
      "Portsmouth,",
      "PO1",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Lloyds",
      "Banking",
      "Group",
      "→",
      "Jul",
      "2013",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3417,
    "tokens": [
      "Position",
      ">",
      "Head",
      "of",
      "Engineering"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1285,
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.:",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "@",
      "VTU",
      "|",
      "2014-2018",
      "|",
      "72.1%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2267,
    "tokens": [
      "Firm",
      ":",
      "Wipro",
      "Cyber",
      "Security"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2989,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "\\\\",
      "Electrical",
      "Engineering",
      "\\\\",
      "NIT",
      "Warangal",
      "\\\\",
      "2013-2017",
      "\\\\",
      "77.9%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3952,
    "tokens": [
      "Delhivery",
      "Pvt.",
      "Ltd.",
      "/",
      "SDE",
      "I",
      "/",
      "Gurgaon",
      "/",
      "Aug",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "Aug",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 477,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "(IT)",
      "–",
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "–",
      "2013",
      "–",
      "74.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 694,
    "tokens": [
      "Mphasis",
      "Technologies",
      "::",
      "Software",
      "Engineer",
      "::",
      "Chennai",
      "::",
      "2016–2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 774,
    "tokens": [
      "mtech",
      "from",
      "iit",
      "madras",
      "2008-2010",
      "cgpa",
      "8.6/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3569,
    "tokens": [
      "Profile",
      "::",
      "Software",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2656,
    "tokens": [
      "Joined",
      "Zenith",
      "Omni",
      "Group",
      "as",
      "Position=Senior",
      "Zero",
      "Trust",
      "Architect",
      "@",
      "Hyderabad",
      "::",
      "Client=Innovative",
      "Analytics",
      "Co.",
      "::",
      "Mar",
      "2021",
      "-",
      "Now"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 537,
    "tokens": [
      "Degree",
      ":",
      "M.Tech"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4448,
    "tokens": [
      "Accenture",
      "|",
      "Junior",
      "Analyst"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 611,
    "tokens": [
      "Hexaware,",
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2775,
    "tokens": [
      "Groww",
      "[Engineering",
      "Manager]",
      "[Bangalore]",
      "[Jan",
      "2023",
      "–",
      "Present]"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 759,
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2157,
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Communications",
      "→",
      "Loyola",
      "University",
      "Chicago",
      "→",
      "2012–2016",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.4"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2725,
    "tokens": [
      "Gainsight",
      "-",
      "VP",
      "of",
      "Product",
      "Operations",
      "-",
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Workday",
      "Inc",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "01/2022",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3118,
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Bombay",
      "::",
      "BCA",
      "::",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "::",
      "Hyderabad",
      "::",
      "2018-2021",
      "::",
      "8.46/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 976,
    "tokens": [
      "Client",
      "##",
      "Rabobank",
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2028,
    "tokens": [
      "Institute",
      ":",
      "College",
      "of",
      "Engineering",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2473,
    "tokens": [
      "Started",
      "career",
      "as",
      "Graduate",
      "Developer",
      "at",
      "Nitro",
      "Software,",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "CA",
      "/",
      "Sydney",
      "NSW",
      "2000",
      "from",
      "March",
      "2012",
      "to",
      "May",
      "2015,",
      "working",
      "for",
      "client",
      "PwC",
      "Australia."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1410,
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.",
      "–",
      "Osmania",
      "University",
      "–",
      "Hyderabad",
      "–",
      "2012-2015",
      "–",
      "76.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1303,
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "Noida",
      "|",
      "2020–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2957,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Sc",
      "–",
      "Information",
      "Technology",
      "Graduated:",
      "2007-2010",
      "|",
      "71.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2022,
    "tokens": [
      "M.S.",
      "Software",
      "Engineering",
      "-",
      "Vanderbilt",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2016",
      "to",
      "2018",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2341,
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Bombay",
      "|",
      "2013–2015",
      "|",
      "88.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3470,
    "tokens": [
      "Health",
      "Strategic",
      "S.A.",
      "[2022–Present]",
      "→",
      "Group",
      "Product",
      "Manager",
      "→",
      "Pune"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4258,
    "tokens": [
      "Vercel,",
      "New",
      "York",
      "NY",
      "—",
      "Sr.",
      "Frontend",
      "Engineer",
      "—",
      "Client:",
      "GitHub",
      "—",
      "Apr",
      "2021",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 676,
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "Medtronic",
      "USA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1423,
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.",
      "–",
      "Mumbai",
      "University",
      "–",
      "Mumbai",
      "–",
      "2010-2013",
      "–",
      "79.3%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 559,
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys",
      "Ltd,",
      "Software",
      "Engineer,",
      "Noida,",
      "2017",
      "-",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1742,
    "tokens": [
      "Client:",
      "ANZ",
      "Bank",
      "Australia"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2964,
    "tokens": [
      "Airbase",
      "→",
      "Senior",
      "Accountant",
      "→",
      "San",
      "Francisco,",
      "CA",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "DoorDash",
      "Inc",
      "→",
      "Sep",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Feb",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3335,
    "tokens": [
      "<Ventures",
      "Financial",
      "Pty",
      "Ltd",
      "-",
      "Cloud",
      "Engineer",
      "(GCP)",
      "-",
      "Hyderabad",
      "-",
      "2015–2019>"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2729,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "CSE",
      "|",
      "2014-2018",
      "|",
      "CGPA",
      "9.2/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3139,
    "tokens": [
      "MBA,",
      "IT",
      ">>",
      "Symbiosis",
      "Pune",
      ">>",
      "2015-2017",
      ">>",
      "8.4",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 355,
    "tokens": [
      "Year",
      ":",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1684,
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology,",
      "Rajasthan",
      "Technical",
      "University,",
      "Kota,",
      "2006-2010,",
      "6.9",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1894,
    "tokens": [
      "Location",
      ":",
      "Hyderabad,",
      "Telangana"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3457,
    "tokens": [
      "JNTU",
      "Hyderabad|",
      "B.Tech",
      "(Mech)",
      "|",
      "HYD",
      "|",
      "2009-2013",
      "|",
      "76%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1182,
    "tokens": [
      "Principal",
      "Healthcare",
      "IT",
      "&",
      "Interoperability",
      "Solutions",
      "Architect"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4432,
    "tokens": [
      "M.S.",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "|",
      "UC",
      "Berkeley",
      "/",
      "2014-2016",
      "|",
      "GPA",
      "3.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1338,
    "tokens": [
      "Junior",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Wipro",
      "Technologies",
      "|",
      "Hyd",
      "|",
      "Apr'17",
      "to",
      "Dec'20"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 826,
    "tokens": [
      "HCL",
      "Technologies"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2252,
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Product",
      "Design",
      "-",
      "Carnegie",
      "Mellon",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2014",
      "to",
      "2016",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.9"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3183,
    "tokens": [
      "IISc",
      "Bangalore",
      ">",
      "M.Tech",
      "Electronics",
      ">",
      "Bangalore",
      ">",
      "2017-2019",
      ">",
      "7.2",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1262,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech:",
      "Computer",
      "Science",
      "@",
      "JNTU",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "2012–2016",
      "|",
      "CGPA:",
      "7.8"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3399,
    "tokens": [
      "(Apex",
      "Neo",
      "Enterprises)",
      "(Data",
      "Scientist)",
      "(client:Future",
      "Systems",
      "Incorporated)",
      "(Chennai)",
      "(2016–2019)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1558,
    "tokens": [
      "Year",
      ":",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1687,
    "tokens": [
      "MBA",
      "→",
      "Georgetown",
      "University",
      "→",
      "2016-2018",
      "→",
      "3.8",
      "GPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "tokens": [
      "Organisation",
      ":",
      "Lockheed",
      "Martin"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1233,
    "tokens": [
      "Jersey",
      "City,",
      "NJ"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1790,
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Economics",
      "-",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Michigan",
      "-",
      "2008",
      "to",
      "2012",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.6"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1827,
    "tokens": [
      "Previously",
      "worked",
      "as",
      "Digital",
      "Marketing",
      "Analyst",
      "at",
      "Bazaarvoice,",
      "Austin,",
      "TX",
      "from",
      "2019",
      "to",
      "2022,",
      "deployed",
      "at",
      "client",
      "Target",
      "Corporation."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1840,
    "tokens": [
      "Inovalon",
      "-",
      "Healthcare",
      "Analyst",
      "-",
      "Bowie,",
      "MD",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Humana",
      "Inc.",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "09/2015",
      "to",
      "01/2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2870,
    "tokens": [
      "Alteryx",
      "→",
      "Senior",
      "Analytics",
      "Engineer",
      "→",
      "Denver,",
      "CO",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Lockheed",
      "Martin",
      "→",
      "Nov",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Apr",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3267,
    "tokens": [
      "What",
      ":",
      "Associate",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2715,
    "tokens": [
      "Bachelor",
      "of",
      "Technology",
      ">>",
      "Stanford",
      "University",
      "[2016–19]",
      "(88%)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 846,
    "tokens": [
      "mtech",
      "embedded",
      "from",
      "iit",
      "delhi",
      "2008-2010",
      "cgpa",
      "8.4/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1195,
    "tokens": [
      "PhD",
      "Computer",
      "Vision",
      "|",
      "IISc",
      "Bengaluru",
      "|",
      "2016–2021",
      "|",
      "Published",
      "4",
      "Papers"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2579,
    "tokens": [
      "::",
      "B.Tech",
      "CSE",
      "|",
      "Amity",
      "University",
      "Noida",
      "|",
      "2013–2017",
      "|",
      "8.2",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 785,
    "tokens": [
      "2016–2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3296,
    "tokens": [
      "Timeframe",
      "|",
      "May",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "October",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1183,
    "tokens": [
      "Associate",
      "@",
      "Infosys",
      "|",
      "Hyd",
      "|",
      "Aug",
      "2014",
      "-",
      "Feb",
      "2016"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2294,
    "tokens": [
      "Aug",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Till",
      "Date",
      "|",
      "Senior",
      "SAP",
      "Consultant",
      "|",
      "Deloitte",
      "USI",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 393,
    "tokens": [
      "B.E.",
      "–",
      "Gujarat",
      "University",
      "–",
      "Ahmedabad",
      "–",
      "2013",
      "–",
      "69.4%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4375,
    "tokens": [
      "Snowflake",
      "|",
      "Sr.",
      "Cloud",
      "Dev",
      "-",
      "San",
      "Mateo",
      "CA",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Capital",
      "One",
      "-",
      "Jan",
      "2022-Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2387,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Sc",
      "/",
      "Data",
      "Science",
      "/",
      "Bangalore",
      "University",
      "/",
      "2012–2016",
      "/",
      "72.8%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1246,
    "tokens": [
      "Microsft",
      "India,Principal",
      "Engineer,Hyderabad,2019,Present,client:LinkedIn"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3710,
    "tokens": [
      "(2)",
      "Swiggy",
      "(Bundl",
      "Tech)",
      "::",
      "SDE-II",
      "::",
      "Bangalore",
      "::",
      "Jun",
      "2018",
      "–",
      "Nov",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3895,
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Delhi",
      "|",
      "M.Tech",
      "CS",
      "|",
      "2017–2019",
      "|",
      "8.9",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4154,
    "tokens": [
      "Period:",
      "Feb",
      "2022–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1462,
    "tokens": [
      "SDE3",
      "|",
      "Org:",
      "Zomato",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Hyperpure",
      "Supply",
      "|",
      "Place:",
      "Gurgaon",
      "|",
      "Duration:",
      "2021-present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3121,
    "tokens": [
      "Soft",
      "Atlantic",
      "Pty",
      "Ltd",
      "::",
      "Associate",
      "Product",
      "Manager",
      "(APM)",
      "::",
      "Pune",
      "::",
      "Sep",
      "2018",
      "→",
      "Oct",
      "2020"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2767,
    "tokens": [
      "Multiverse",
      "|",
      "Learning",
      "Experience",
      "Designer",
      "|",
      "London,",
      "E1W",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Deloitte",
      "UK",
      "|",
      "2021–Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1378,
    "tokens": [
      "(2)",
      "Microsoft",
      "Azure",
      "|",
      "Cloud",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "Jul",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "Feb",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3207,
    "tokens": [
      "→",
      "NIT",
      "Trichy",
      "/",
      "B.Tech",
      "CSE",
      "/",
      "2013–2017",
      "/",
      "8.6",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 671,
    "tokens": [
      "Master",
      "of",
      "Science:Cybersecurity>Georgia",
      "Institute",
      "of",
      "Technology>Atlanta",
      "GA>2015>2017"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2709,
    "tokens": [
      "Sprout",
      "Social",
      "-",
      "Regional",
      "Sales",
      "Director",
      "-",
      "Austin,",
      "TX",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Dell",
      "Technologies",
      "-",
      "02/2023",
      "to",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2153,
    "tokens": [
      "BS",
      "Computer",
      "Information",
      "Systems",
      "-",
      "Brigham",
      "Young",
      "University",
      "-",
      "2011",
      "to",
      "2015",
      "-",
      "GPA",
      "3.5"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4170,
    "tokens": [
      "Role",
      ":",
      "Data",
      "Scientist"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2047,
    "tokens": [
      "Revolut",
      "|",
      "Product",
      "Manager",
      "|",
      "London,",
      "W1T",
      "|",
      "Client:",
      "Barclays",
      "PLC",
      "|",
      "2018–2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4132,
    "tokens": [
      "Worked",
      "as",
      "Data",
      "Platform",
      "Dev",
      "at",
      "MapR",
      "Technologies",
      "in",
      "San",
      "Jose,",
      "CA",
      "from",
      "Aug",
      "2019",
      "to",
      "Dec",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4500,
    "tokens": [
      "Siemens",
      "Healthineers",
      "India",
      "|",
      "Software",
      "Architect",
      "|",
      "Bangalore",
      "|",
      "Mar",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1980,
    "tokens": [
      "COMPANY",
      ":",
      "Rolta",
      "India"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1407,
    "tokens": [
      "Score",
      ":",
      "86.2%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2461,
    "tokens": [
      "Earlier",
      "served",
      "as",
      "Application",
      "Security",
      "Analyst",
      "at",
      "Adzuna,",
      "Birmingham",
      "from",
      "Mar",
      "2018",
      "to",
      "Aug",
      "2022."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 839,
    "tokens": [
      "Infosys,",
      "Bangalore"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3810,
    "tokens": [
      "5paisa",
      "Capital",
      "Ltd.",
      "SDE",
      "I",
      "Mumbai",
      "2017.07",
      "–",
      "2019.07"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 415,
    "tokens": [
      "iGate|Bangalore",
      "India|Software",
      "Developer|September",
      "2014|March",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-ROLE",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3162,
    "tokens": [
      "IIT",
      "Bombay",
      "::",
      "B.Tech",
      "Data",
      "Science",
      "::",
      "Pune",
      "::",
      "2013-2016",
      "::",
      "82%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1949,
    "tokens": [
      "FourKites",
      "→",
      "Freight",
      "Analytics",
      "Specialist",
      "→",
      "Chicago,",
      "IL",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Kraft",
      "Heinz",
      "Company",
      "→",
      "May",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "Jul",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 269,
    "tokens": [
      "Role",
      ":",
      "Sr.",
      "Full",
      "Stack",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1075,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "Electronics",
      "&",
      "Communication",
      "@",
      "IIT",
      "Delhi,",
      "New",
      "Delhi,",
      "completed",
      "2008-2012,",
      "8.8",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 434,
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech:Machine",
      "Learning,IIT",
      "Madras,Chennai",
      "India(2016-2018)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4227,
    "tokens": [
      "[2013-2017]",
      "B.S.",
      "Computer",
      "Science,",
      "UNC",
      "Chapel",
      "Hill,",
      "GPA",
      "3.4"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2937,
    "tokens": [
      "Graduated:",
      "2002-2007"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 626,
    "tokens": [
      "M.Tech",
      "Software",
      "Engineering",
      "–",
      "BITS",
      "Pilani",
      "–",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "8.6",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 942,
    "tokens": [
      "Sr.",
      "Platform",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Swiggy",
      "|",
      "Bangalore,",
      "Karnataka",
      "|",
      "Feb",
      "2023",
      "-",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1487,
    "tokens": [
      "Location",
      ":",
      "Bengaluru"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1248,
    "tokens": [
      "Broadcom,Embedded",
      "SW",
      "Eng,Bengaluru,2011,2015,client:Cisco"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1853,
    "tokens": [
      "SCORE",
      ":",
      "71.5%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1090,
    "tokens": [
      "Associate",
      "Director",
      "–",
      "Technology",
      "|",
      "Vantage",
      "Biotech",
      "Solutions",
      "|",
      "2017",
      "–",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4033,
    "tokens": [
      "IIIT",
      "Bangalore",
      ">>",
      "M.Tech",
      "Health",
      "Informatics",
      ">>",
      "2017–2019",
      ">>",
      "8.8",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2879,
    "tokens": [
      "Faculty",
      "AI",
      "-",
      "ML",
      "Research",
      "Engineer",
      "-",
      "London,",
      "W1B",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Cabinet",
      "Office",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "04/2016",
      "to",
      "12/2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 566,
    "tokens": [
      "Jan",
      "2013",
      "–",
      "Mar",
      "2015"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2396,
    "tokens": [
      "EXP={company:\"Greentree",
      "International\",",
      "title:\"Junior",
      "Developer\",",
      "city:\"Auckland",
      "NZ\",",
      "from:2016,",
      "to:2019}"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2434,
    "tokens": [
      "Whispir",
      "→",
      "DevOps",
      "Engineer",
      "→",
      "Melbourne,",
      "VIC",
      "3000",
      "→",
      "Client:",
      "Telstra",
      "Corporation",
      "→",
      "Mar",
      "2016",
      "–",
      "May",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1047,
    "tokens": [
      "Sr.",
      "Systems",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Infosys",
      "|",
      "Hyderabad",
      "|",
      "January",
      "2021",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 815,
    "tokens": [
      "btech",
      "it",
      "from",
      "jntu",
      "hyderabad",
      "2007-2010",
      "marks:72%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 562,
    "tokens": [
      "Apr",
      "2015",
      "–",
      "Mar",
      "2018"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 575,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech",
      "(Electronics",
      "&",
      "CS)",
      "–",
      "NIT",
      "Karnataka",
      "–",
      "Surathkal",
      "–",
      "2012",
      "–",
      "8.5",
      "CGPA"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4421,
    "tokens": [
      "Booking.com",
      "!",
      "Junior",
      "Dev",
      "!",
      "New",
      "York",
      "NY",
      "!",
      "Mar",
      "2016-Jul",
      "2019"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4190,
    "tokens": [
      "GitHub",
      "(Microsoft)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1087,
    "tokens": [
      "B.Tech:",
      "ECE",
      "@",
      "NIT",
      "Warangal",
      "|",
      "2011–2015",
      "|",
      "CGPA:",
      "8.1/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3770,
    "tokens": [
      "NIT",
      "Trichy",
      ">>",
      "B.Tech",
      "ECE",
      ">>",
      "2012–2016",
      ">>",
      "8.7/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2248,
    "tokens": [
      "Role",
      ":",
      "Software",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2143,
    "tokens": [
      "Anna",
      "University",
      "|",
      "M.E.",
      "CSE",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "2016–2018",
      "|",
      "9.2/10"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1287,
    "tokens": [
      "Phoenix,",
      "AZ"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2724,
    "tokens": [
      "Intern",
      "@",
      "Financial",
      "Cloud",
      "S.A.",
      "::",
      "Position=Junior",
      "Red",
      "Team",
      "Engineer",
      "::",
      "Client=None",
      "::",
      "Hyderabad",
      "::",
      "Jan",
      "2021",
      "-",
      "Jan",
      "2021"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4022,
    "tokens": [
      "Acko",
      "General",
      "Insurance",
      "Principal",
      "Engineer",
      "Bangalore",
      "Nov",
      "2022",
      "–",
      "Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "tokens": [
      "June20",
      "–",
      "Februar",
      "UI",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2552,
    "tokens": [
      "M.S.",
      "Information",
      "Systems",
      "→",
      "University",
      "of",
      "Southern",
      "California",
      "→",
      "2013–2015",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.7"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4370,
    "tokens": [
      "Twilio",
      "$",
      "Sr.",
      "API",
      "Dev",
      "$",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "CA",
      "$",
      "Client:",
      "Lyft",
      "$",
      "Jan",
      "2023-Present"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2958,
    "tokens": [
      "Benchmark",
      "Holdings",
      "-",
      "Aquaculture",
      "Specialist",
      "-",
      "Edinburgh,",
      "EH6",
      "-",
      "Client:",
      "Marine",
      "Harvest",
      "UK",
      "-",
      "Since",
      "02/2019",
      "to",
      "07/2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4519,
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "RF",
      "Engineer",
      "|",
      "Chennai",
      "|",
      "Jan",
      "2019",
      "–",
      "Feb",
      "2022"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2164,
    "tokens": [
      "Mastek",
      "Ltd."
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "tokens": [
      "Title",
      ":",
      "API",
      "Developer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1080,
    "tokens": [
      "Portland,",
      "OR"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1016,
    "tokens": [
      "BSc",
      "Geology@BHU",
      "Varanasi@Varanasi@2005@2008@percentage:74%"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2722,
    "tokens": [
      "Joined",
      "Agile",
      "Government",
      "Corporation",
      "as",
      "Position=Senior",
      "SDK",
      "Engineer",
      "@",
      "Bangalore",
      "::",
      "Client=Superior",
      "Zenith",
      "Incorporated",
      "::",
      "Oct",
      "2023",
      "-",
      "Now"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "O",
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 925,
    "tokens": [
      "Geometric",
      "Software",
      ">>",
      "Senior",
      "Solution",
      "Architect",
      ">>",
      "starting",
      "from",
      "Aug",
      "2020",
      "still",
      "working",
      ">>",
      "Bangalore",
      "Client",
      ">>",
      "Rolls",
      "Royce",
      "UK"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "I-START_DATE",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "I-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 928,
    "tokens": [
      "IBM",
      "INDIA",
      "|",
      "Full",
      "Stack",
      "Lead",
      "|",
      "2018/05",
      "–",
      "Current",
      "|",
      "Bengaluru"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "O",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "O",
      "B-START_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2172,
    "tokens": [
      "MS",
      "Industrial-Organizational",
      "Psychology",
      "→",
      "Seattle",
      "Pacific",
      "University",
      "→",
      "2015–2017",
      "→",
      "GPA",
      "3.7"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-DEGREE",
      "B-DEGREE",
      "I-DEGREE",
      "O",
      "B-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "I-EDUCATION",
      "O",
      "B-END_DATE",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-DEGREE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3379,
    "tokens": [
      "(Green",
      "Dynamic",
      "LLC)",
      "(Senior",
      "NLP",
      "Engineer)",
      "(client:Bank",
      "Stellar",
      "Pty",
      "Ltd)",
      "(Chennai)",
      "(2017–2021)"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "I-COMPANY",
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE",
      "B-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "I-CLIENT",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "B-END_DATE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 690,
    "tokens": [
      "Senior",
      "Engineer"
    ],
    "ner_tags": [
      "B-ROLE",
      "I-ROLE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3027,
    "tokens": [
      "B.E",
      "–",
      "Electronics",
